感谢之前在射手网上传英文字幕和繁体中文字幕的朋友，
本字母是参考以上两个字幕制作而成的
发现做字幕是一件很麻烦的事情，因此每当你下载
一个好的字幕时，你都应该在心中感谢那些字幕制作者们
☆ 找水的鱼☆制作
Daddy, please! You're not helping!
老爸，拜托！你在帮倒忙！
I looked into his eyes.
Not the eyes of a man.
我看过他的眼睛。
那不是男人的眼神。
The eyes of a coward.
那是懦夫的眼神
(speaking in Thai again)
（泰文）
Excuse me!
对不起！
- Bill!
- Tracy!
-比尔
-特蕾西
- I'm sorry!
- Where the hell are you?
- 对不起！
- 你到底在哪里？
It happened again!
我们又出包了！
Don't say that, please!
不会吧
No this time we really fucked up.
这一次，我们真的搞砸了。
Seriously! What is wrong with you three?
说真的！你们3个到底有甚麽毛病啊？
So much Trace, I don't even know
where to begin.
太复杂了，我不知从何说起
Oh god! How bad?
哦，天啊！有多糟糕？
- Like, no wedding bad?
- Yeah...
- 像是....无法举办婚礼？
- 啊...
a little worse than that.
还更糟一点点。
THE HANGOVER PART II
ONE WEEK EARLIER
一个星期前
Uh, huh.
- You really need to floss more.
- Fuck that! That's why I come here.
- 你真的该多用牙线。
- 谁鸟它！不然我来这里干嘛。
- Then you should come more than once every two years!
- Why? So you can bleed me of all my money?
- 那你应该每两年多来几次！
- 为什麽？这样你就可以榨乾我的钱吗？
I never charge you a dime, Phil!
我从来没收过你一毛钱，菲尔！
- Hey, how do I work the nitrous?
- Ah, you don't actually.
- 嘿，怎麽没给我麻醉一下？
- 啊，其实你用不到。
Come on! Just one hit!
来啦！弄一下！
Fillings look pretty good. Any other problems?
牙齿补得很好。还有其他问题吗？
Yeah, actually. You're getting married
in Thailand.
有。你要在泰国结婚了。
For starters, that's flights for me and Steph.
That's two grand right there.
一开始来说，我和与Steph需要飞出去。
两个重点就在这里了。
Then my mother in laws watching the kids. So
now she's got this whole new thing over my head.
然後，我岳母要带孩子。因此，
现在我的脑袋塞满了这件事。
Plus, takes five days to get there.
另外，需要五天的时间才能到达那里。
It's a 16 hour flight. And it's beautiful
when you get there.
只要飞16的小时就到了。
你到那里就会知道那是个美丽的地方
- Whatever, it's a hassle!
- It is kinda far.
- 不管怎样，就是很麻烦！
- 是有点远。
Lauren's been there a week and she's
still jet lagged.
萝拉已经过去一个星期了，她还是有时差反应。
But it's where her parents are from and
it means a lot to them.
但那是她父母的故乡 对他们意义很大。
Who gives a shit about her parents!
Her dad hates you!
谁鸟他爸妈！
她爸讨厌你！
He doesn't hate me! He's just never
spoken to me...
他不讨厌我！
他只是从来没有跟我说过话 ...
...I think it's a cultural thing.
...我认为这是文化的关系。
Why can't you just get married in Vegas like
you did the last time. It's so much easier.
为什麽你就不能像上次在赌城结婚一样
不就简单多了
Why can't you just be excited for me?
为什麽你就不能替我感到兴奋？
This is my wedding!
这是我的婚礼！
- You're really happy, huh?
- I really am.
- 你真的很开心，对吧？
- 没错。
Alright...
好吧...
...I'm happy too.
...我也很开心。
- Thank you!
- Gonna be fun.
- 谢谢你！
- 会很好玩的。
Phil. Put the prescription pad back.
菲尔。把处方笺拿回来。
- Thank you. You know that's a felony right?
- Fuck you, man!
- 谢谢。你知道这是犯法的吧？
- 操你妈的！
- Was this right up against your scrotum?
- Yep.
- 你把它放在你蛋蛋旁边吗？
- 没错。
- Oh my god, I just realized.
- What?
- 哦，天啊，我现在才发现。
- 什麽？
- I forgot to renew my passport!
- Oh no...
- 我忘了申请延长护照期限！
- 哦，不...
Good thing I did it last week. It's in
the kitchen drawer.
还好我上星期去申请了。它放在厨房的抽屉。
- You're the best!
- Hey! We're a team!
- 你是最棒的！
- 嘿！我们是一起的！
You're a good guy. Like a really good guy!
你是个好人。像一个真正的好人！
Thank you!
谢谢！
- So I know you're not gonna get mad.
- Mad? What, mad at what?
- 我知道你不会生气。
- 疯了吗？什麽，生什麽气？
Alan found out that we're going to
Thailand for Stu's wedding.
艾伦发现，我们将去泰国 参加史都的婚礼。
- So?
- So he's heart broken Doug. You guys are like his family!
- 那又怎样??？
- 因此，他的心碎了 道格。你们就像他的家人！
No. Your family is like his family.
不 你的家人才像他的家人。
All Alan talks about is the three of you.
艾伦一直再说你们三个。
- And that weekend.
- Wait a second...
- 还有这个周末。
- 等一下 ...
- Is he the one who keeps calling and hanging up?
- He does that when he's upset.
- 他是不是一直打电话来再挂断？
- 当他不快乐时 他就这麽做。
He doesn't understand why he's not invited.
他不明白他为什麽不被邀请。
Could you just run it by Stu? Just run it by him.
你能不能透过史都邀请他？透过他。
For me...
为我邀请他 ...
No fucking way! Absolutely not!
他妈的没有办法！绝对不可能！
Come on Stu, it's killing him.
拜托 史都，这会杀了他。
Honestly, the two of you were barely invited.
老实说，你们两个人也几乎不算被邀请。
I get it. I really do. It's just, you know what...
我明白了。真的。这只是，你知道吗 ...
Alan considers you to be one of his best friends.
艾伦认为你是他的一个最好的朋友。
I consider Alan to be insane.
我认为艾伦是疯了。
Stu, throw him a bone! We've already said he's got to
pay for everything he eats and everything he breaks.
史都，给他一点希望嘛！我们已经表示，他吃的和他打坏的都得付钱。
You know what. We should see if we can squeeze
the old man to cover the bachelor party.
你知道吗。我们可以看到，如果我们从那老人身上榨出办单身派对的钱。
- That's good.
- I'm glad you brought that up.
- 这很好。
- 我很高兴你提到这个。
- Because... this is the bachelor party!
- What?
- 因为 ...这就是单身派对！
- 什麽？
- What are you talking about?
- Yeah, it's my bachelor brunch!
- 你在说什麽啊？
- 是的，这就是我的光棍早午餐！
Go crazy. Get some chocolate chip pancakes... a
lap dance from the waitress...
疯一下。拿一些巧克力煎饼 ...服务生跳一下艳舞 ...
That's bullshit! You can't just skip
out of a bachelor party, Stu.
这是狗屎！你不能只跳过了单身派对，史都。
You see that? That's orange juice with
a napkin on top.
你看到了吗？这是柳橙汁 餐巾放在上面。
Do you know why? So nobody will refuse me.
你知道为什麽吗？因此，没有人会拒绝我。
Why I refuse to eat fucking cantaloupe
at a bachelor party?
为什麽我会在一个单身派对 拒绝吃他妈的哈密瓜？
- C'mon Stu. Don't you think you're over reacting?
- No, I don't.
- 拜托 史都。难道你不觉得你过度反应了？
- 不，我不觉得。
I'm still putting the pieces of my broken
psyche back together.
我还是在将我破碎的心灵碎片重新黏到一起。
And you know what the glue is? Lauren!
I'm not doing anything to screw that up.
而你知道什麽是胶水吗？ 是萝拉！
我不会做任何事来搞砸它。
- Oh, please. You wouldn't even be with her if it wasn't for us.
- Oh, this'll be good.
- 哦，拜托。如果没有我们 你甚至不会跟她在一起。
- 噢，这将会很好。
Stu, think about it!
史都，想想吧！
You ended up ditching Melissa, and two years later
you met your true soul mate.
你和蒙莉莎分手，两年後 你遇见真正的心灵伴侣。
You take Vegas out of that equation, you
would have married a cunt.
你去拉斯维加斯才走出这个关系，你本来会娶到一个婊子。
Oh that's ok. I'm allowed to say it. It's
a bachelor party.
噢，那没关系。我可以说那个。因为这是单身派对。
Drink up everybody.
大家喝起来。
Oh wait, there's no alcohol! I forgot
we're at a fuckin IHOP!
哦，等等，没有酒精！我忘了
我们现在在一家他妈的IHOP餐厅！
Well it's my decision and it's final, so...
how bout a toast?
那麽这是我的决定，就这样，所以...举杯庆祝一下如何？
This sucks. I'm gonna wait in the car.
烂毙了。我要在车里等。
- C'mon Phil, where you going?
- Doug, Doug, I just don't get it!
- 来吧 菲尔，你要去哪？
- 道，道格，我还是不明白！
He's getting married in Thailand! That's
great for him, but what about us?
他要去泰国结婚！非常适合他，但我们呢？
You're selfish! Come on, sweetheart...
你真是自私！来吧，亲爱的...
Shame on you!
你应感到羞耻！
Don't worry Stu. I will stand up for you
no matter what.
不用担心史都。我会支持你 不论如何。
Thank you.
But you gotta help me out with this Alan thing.
但你得帮我这个艾伦的事。
Guys, I can't tell you how much this means...
夥计们，我无法告诉你们 这对他多麽 ...
Alan's been waiting for the invite ever
since he got word of the wedding.
艾伦一直在等待婚礼的邀请
当他一听到婚礼的消息。
- I'm sure he has.
- Yeah.
- 我相信他会。
- 是啊。
Been standing outside by the mailbox every day.
每天都站在外面的信箱。
- Well that's tough.
- Yeah.
- 嗯 这倒是很难的。
- 是啊。
I uh, I'm not sure he ever left Vegas.
我，嗯，我不知道他是否会离开拉斯维加斯。
He really needs this.
他真的需要这个。
What?
什麽？
Sweetie, papa! You have visitors!
Go in slowly.
亲爱的，是爸爸！你有客人！
谈慢一点
Give him a chance to acclimate.
给他一个机会重新调整。
- Hey, Alan!
- Hey, guys! Hey, Phil!
- 嘿，艾伦！
- 嗨，夥计们！嘿，菲尔！
Hey, bud!
嘿，哥们！
- You guys wanna come in?
- Sure. Absolutely.
- 你们要进来吗？
- 当然。绝对要。
- Hey.
- 嘿。
- 嘿，史都！
- 确定。在球场上等你在半...
- Pretty cool room, Alan!
- Thanks, Phil! My dad pays my rent.
- 很酷的房间，艾伦！
- 谢谢，菲尔！我爸爸支付房租。
Alan, what the fuck! You were supposed
to delete these!
艾伦，搞甚麽！你应该删掉这些照片！
You made a promise!
你承诺过的！
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
哇，哇，哇！
What the hell? I'm not cool with this
at all. You can't have these.
搞啥啊？看到这我怎麽能冷静
你不能留下这些东西
Relax, Stu! Nobody ever comes in here.
放松，史都！从来没人会来这里。
- A total violation of trust!
- Mother I'm done with my lunch. It's just sitting here!
- 违背了我们之间的信赖！
- 妈，我吃完了午餐。我坐在这里等你！
I'm sorry, honey. I'll be right up.
对不起，亲爱的。我马上上来。
- I can't believe you guys stopped by. This is really cool.
- Wait a second!
- 艾伦，这是周先生吗？
- 是啊。我们仍然保持联络。
- Al, is that Mr. Chow?
- Yeah. We still keep in touch.
Stu!
史都！
Chow, the guy that kidnapped us?
老周？那个绑架我们的家夥？
He didn't kidnap us. He kidnapped Black Doug.
他没有绑架我们。他绑架的是黑色的道格。
Remember? It was a whole big misunderstanding.
还记得吗？这整个就是个大误会。
He's actually quite charming.
他其实很迷人。
- Alan, he's a criminal.
- Excuse me, boys!
- 艾伦，他是一个罪犯。
- 不好意思，孩子们！
- Hi, Linda!
- Hi, Dougie!
- 嗨，琳达！
- 嗨，小道！
I guess we don't do desert anymore. I
didn't get that memo.
我以为我们没有点心了。我没收到通知。
I'm sorry, darling. I'll be right back.
对不起，亲爱的。我马上就回来。
Would a cupcake kill you?
多放个蛋糕会杀了你？
- You know, I don't think this was a good idea.
- Alan, we have a little surprise for you.
- 你知道，我不认为这是一个好主意。
- 艾伦，我们有一点点惊喜要给你。
Stu would like to invite you to his wedding.
史都想邀请你参加他的婚礼。
- Well only if you're not busy.
- Stu!
- 嗯，如果你不太忙的话。
- 史都！
Well maybe the Jonas Brothers are in town.
嗯，也许乔纳斯兄弟在城里演唱。
Nope. They're in Raleigh-Durham that weekend.
不。他们这周在Raleigh - Durham。
Are you really being serious, Stu?
You're inviting me?
你真的是认真的吗，史都？ 真的要邀请我吗？
Yeah why not? It's gonna be fun, right?
是啊，为什麽不呢？这会很好玩，对不对？
- Phil, are you going?
- Of course!
- 菲尔，你去不去？
- 当然！
Then it will be fun.
然後，这会很有趣。
What the fuck are you doing, man?
你他妈的你在干什麽，夥计？
It's my immunizations. It's the last day
I can do it.
这是我的免疫接种。这是我最後能做到一点。
That's supposed to be done by a registered nurse.
这应该是由一个注册护士来做。
I'm a nurse. Just not registered.
我是一名护士。只要没有登记。
Stu, look at this!
I bought this cause I thought of you!
史都，看看这个！
我买了这个，因为我想到了你！
- Hey, there he is!
- Hey, Stu!
- 嘿，他在那儿！
- 嘿，史都！
- Teddy! What's up? How are ya?
- Hey Stu.
- 泰迪！还好吧？你好吗？
- 嘿 史都。
- Alright. Who's this guy, Stu?
- This is Teddy. Lauren's little brother.
- 好吧。谁是这家夥，史都？
- 这是泰迪。萝拉的弟弟。
Goes to Stanford. Pre-med. This is
Phil, Alan and Doug.
斯坦福大学。医学预科。这是
菲尔，艾伦和道格。
Hey, nice to meet you, man!
嘿，很高兴见到你，老兄！
Wow, Stanford? How old are you?
哇，斯坦福？你多大了？
- He's 17. Kind of a genius.
- Actually, I'm 16.
- 他17岁大。天才的一种。
- 其实，我是16。
I'm not a genius. My dad just had me take
the entrance exams early.
我不是天才。我爸爸之前才叫我去考入学考试。
Because you're a genius.
因为你是个天才。
- So what are you, a doctor?
- No, not yet. I'm premed.
- 那麽，你是医生吗？
- 不，还没有。我是医学预科。
- Ever heard of that guy Doogie Howser?
- Yeah.
- 你听过那个家夥 叫杜奇豪瑟？
- 是啊。
- Well, he turned out to be a gay.
- Alan.
- 哦，他出柜成为同性恋。
- 艾伦。
It's true, I read it in Teen People.
这是真的，我在Teen People杂志读到过。
Right, ok... well I'm gonna grab a book or something
for the plane. You guys want anything?
对，好...我要拿本书或什麽东西上飞机。你们想要什麽？
- No, thanks. I'm good.
- I would actually love a small water.
- 不，谢谢。我很好。
- 我真的喜爱小瓶水。
Cool.
酷。
- What's the matter with you. He's 16 years old.
- Yeah, Alan. Take it easy!
- 你是怎麽回事。他才16岁。
- 是啊，艾伦。别紧张！
I'm a little confused. Is he here just to
see us off or what. How does this work?
我有点糊涂了。他在这儿只是要替我们送行或什麽。这是如何进行的？
- How does what work?
- Is that person coming to the wedding?
- 什麽东西如何进行？
- 他是要去参加婚礼吗？
Yes Alan. My brides little brother is
coming to the wedding. Is that ok with you?
是的 艾伦。我的新娘的小弟弟是要去参加婚礼。你觉得可以吗？
Well, it's the first time I've heard of it.
You could have paged me.
嗯，这是我第一次听说过。
你可以再传呼我。
Don't over react. It's gonna be fine.
不要过度反应。没事的。
- Hey. Mind if I sit?
- Wolf pack only. Find another chair.
- 嘿。介意我坐这吗？
- 只有狼群可以。去找另一把椅子。
- There's no wolfpack, Alan. C'mon.
- It's no problem. I'll find...
- 没有狼群，艾伦。来吧。
- 这是没有问题的。我会找到...
- Teddy, don't be ridiculous! You're sitting here!
- Careful, that's a Louis...
- 泰迪，别傻了！你坐在这里！
- 小心，那是个LV...
That is a Louis Vuitton!
这是一个LV包包！
- That's a nice neck roll!
- Thanks! You can use it if you want.
- 这是一个不错的睡枕！
- 谢谢！你可以使用它，如果你想要的。
Ok.
好的。
The Downeaster 'Alexa'" by Billy Joel playing
背景音乐 " by Billy Joel演唱The Downeaster 'Alexa'
Baby!
宝贝！
This is so absolutely beautiful!
Thank you much!
这里是绝对地漂亮！谢谢了！
Of course.
当然啦。
Between Teddy and me, you must be pretty excited.
Pretty soon you'll have 2 doctors in the family.
泰迪和我，你一定很兴奋。
很快你就会有2名医生在家庭中。
You have to realize that in my country we
don't consider dentists to be real doctors.
你必须认识到，在我国，我们不认为牙医是真正的医生。
Dad...
Ok.
Anyway I have to go and talk to Teddy
about his cello performance tonight.
反正我要回去跟泰迪谈谈他今晚的大提琴表演。
Ouch!
哎哟！
I'm so sorry...
我很抱歉...
Your dad's kind of obsessed with your
brother, isn't he?
你爸爸是不是对你弟弟很痴迷，不是吗？
Teddy is my dad's prize possession. It's
always been that way.
泰迪是我爸爸占有的珍藏品。一直是这样。
He'll warm up, I promise! Okay?
他会越来越热情的，我保证！好吗？
You can just fax it over to me. I'll
pick it up at the concierge.
你只需传真过来给我。我会去柜台拿的。
Thanks, papa! Bye bye!
谢谢你，爸爸！再见！
That was my dad. I'm a stay at home son.
这是我的爸爸。我是待在家里的儿子。
We were discussing your wedding gift.
He's sparing no expense.
我们在讨论你的结婚礼物。
他会不惜一切代价。
Oh... That's so unnecessary.
哦...实在没有必要的。
I've been meaning to ask someone. I
notice this is a fishing village.
我一直想问别人。我注意这里是一个渔村。
Is there a Long John Silver's on
the island?
岛上是否有Long John Silver餐厅？
You know. No, I don't think so. I'm so sorry.
你知道。没有，我觉得没有。我很抱歉。
But, we are actually serving some
great fresh seafood.
但是，我们实际上有提供一些好吃的新鲜海鲜。
- Better than Long John's?
- Yes.
- 比Long John Silver的更好？
- 是的。
- I'll be the judge of that. Enjoy your evening.
- You too. Ok.
- 我会自行判断的。享受你的夜晚。
- 你也一样。好的。
All right!
Thank you, Teddy!
The hands of a brilliant musician!
伟大音乐家的技术！
And one day, a great surgeon.
而有一天，会是伟大的外科医生。
I admit it...
我承认这一点 ...
When I first met Stu, I was not quite sold.
当我第一次见到史都，我不太想接受他。
He seemed unattractive. He lacked
intelligence and imagination.
他似乎没有吸引力。他缺乏智慧和想像力。
He was missing the spark you look for
in a man.
没有在一个人身上应有的火花。
But then I looked into Stu's eyes.
但後来我看着史都的眼睛。
It reminded me of my sweet brother,
Chai Yo.
让我想起了我可爱的弟弟，柴育。
For those who do not know, Chai Yo is learning
the sailboat and lives in a group home.
对於那些不认识他的人，柴育学习帆船，生活在大家庭里。
But Chai Yo loves "khao" .
但是，柴育热爱「米汁」。
And that's when I realized, Stu is "khao".
这时候我才意识到，史都是「米汁」。
What is "khao"?
什麽是「米汁」？
"Khao" is soft white rice in luke warm water.
「米汁」是软的白米饭浸在温水。
It has no taste.
它没有味道。
We feed it to small baby and uh, very
old people.
我们拿来喂小宝宝，嗯，还有很老的老人。
It is nourishment that everyone can digest.
这是每个人都可以消化的营养。
The world needs "khao", just as the
world needs people like Stu.
世界需要「米汁」，正如
世界需要人们喜欢史都。
To my sweet daughter and Stu!
Congratulations!
为了我可爱的女儿和史都！
恭喜！
Cheers!
And now I believe that Teddy has
something to say.
现在我相信泰迪有话要说。
Sit down! I got this.
Sit down, boy!
坐下！我来。
坐下来，孩子！
That was a.. a great speech, sir!
那是..一段伟大的演说，先生！
I like the comparison between
Stu and rice.
我喜欢史都和稻米的比较。
I've also prepared a few words.
我还准备了几句话。
Hey everybody. Here's some fun facts.
各位，来听些趣事
The population in Thailand is 63 million people.
泰国人口有6300万
It is twice the size of Wyoming.
面积是怀俄明州的两倍。
It's chief exports are textiles, footwear
and rice.
它的主要出口是纺织品，鞋和稻米
Each year approximately 13,000 people are
killed in car accidents in Thailand.
每年约有13,000人在在泰国因车祸身亡
- The climate in Thailand...
- Alan!
- 在泰国的气候 ...
- 艾伦！
- Why don't you skip to the last card there, buddy.
- Okay. Sorry!
- 你为什麽不直接从最後一张卡说
- 好。对不起！
None of you know Stu like I do.
没人比我更了解史都
Not you... not you... not you...
不是你...不是你...不是你...
Not nobody knows Stu like I do.
没人比我更了解史都
No one!
没有人！
I can't even tell you what we've been
through cause we made a pact.
我不能透漏我的们荒唐往事
因为我们讲好不说
More important than blood.
比血缘更重要。
What I can tell you is this. This is
not Stu's first marriage.
我只能告诉各位
这不是史都第一次结婚。
There was a whore in Las Vegas
a couple of years ago.
几年前在赌城有个妓女...
Sit down...
坐下 ...
- Enough! He'll get over it!
- Okay. Thanks, Phil!
- 够了！他会挺过来的！
- 好。谢谢你，菲尔！
In your face!
管他的！
Well that was exactly as painful as I
expected it to be.
这跟我预期的一样痛苦。
Sorry...
- Oh, rice pudding! What are you doing?
- HaHa. Very funny!
- 哦，八宝粥！你在干什麽？
- 哈哈。非常有趣！
Be nice, Phil! He's extra sensitive tonight.
太好了，菲尔！他今晚格外敏感。
Get over it! He's your father in law. He's
supposed to hate you.
克服它！他是你的公公。他应该恨你。
Come have a drink with me and the guys.
来吧，来跟我和大伙们喝一杯。
You know... I'm really exhausted. We're
just gonna go upstairs and crash.
你知道...我真的很疲惫了。我们准备上楼然後崩溃。
C'mon, I just spoke with the manager. He's
gonna let us have a bonfire on the beach.
来吧，我跟经理说了。他会让我们有一个海滩篝火。
That sounds fun!
这听起来很有趣！
- Nyah... I'm good.
- He's tired!
- 尼亚 ...我很好。
- 他累了！
Stu, one drink with your friends who
came all this way.
史都，和你的朋友喝一杯吧 他们都来了。
- I just wanna hang out with you!
- Oh c'mon. Just go! And do me a favor.
- 我只是想和你出去玩！
- 哦，走吧。去吧！并帮我一个忙。
Take Teddy with you. He never gets to
have any fun.
带泰迪一起出去。不然他永远不会去找乐趣。
That is a great idea. Bring the kid.
这是一个好主意。带上孩子。
- Alright. One drink!
- Perfect.
- 好吧。喝一杯！
- 太好了。
- See you later.
- Have fun!
- 再见。
- 玩得开心！
- You have the key?
- Yep, got it right here!
- 你有钥匙吗？
- 是的，就在这里！
I'll see you in 20 minutes!
在20分钟後回来！
My uncle Roger said that he once saw
an albino polar bear.
我的叔叔罗杰说，他曾看见一只白子北极熊。
Really? Polar bears are white.
How would he know if it's an albino?
真的吗？北极熊是白色的。
他怎麽知道这是否是一个患白化病？
This one was black.
这一只是黑色的
Did you ever think maybe it was
just a black bear?
你是否想过也许只是一只黑熊？
Whatever...
不管
Ok. Here we go. American beer.
好的。来了。美国啤酒。
- Sealed bottle!
- Thank you. Alright!
- 密封瓶！
- 谢谢你。好吧！
- I'm not really old enough to drink.
- Yeah, it's illegal.
- 我年纪没有达到喝酒的年龄。
- 是的，这是非法的。
Would be a shame if somebody reported you.
如果有人举报你 那将是羞耻的事。
Nobody's reporting anybody.
It's fine Teddy. Have a little fun.
没有人会去检举。没关系 泰迪。开心一点。
Careful!
小心！
What is this? Instant marshmallows?
Nice touch!
这是什麽？速食棉花糖？干的好！
- That was Alan's idea.
- Good thinking, Al!
- 这是Alan的主意。
- 好主意，Al！
You know... I gotta hand it to you, Stu!
This place is paradise.
你知道...我不禁要说，史都！
这个地方就是天堂。
Not bad, right?
没坏吧？
And I can't believe I'm saying this,
but I'm actually jealous of you.
而且我不能相信我会这样说，
但实际上，我嫉妒你。
- I mean, Lauren is an angel.
- Yeah, she really is amazing.
- 我的意思是，萝拉是个天使。
- 是啊，她真的令人难以置信。
Wow, you guys are sweet.
哇，你俩真是甜蜜。
Not big breasts on her. But still, solid
rack for an Asian.
她的乳房并不大。但尽管如此，以亚洲人来说也够硬的。
- Sorry, Teddy, but it's true.
- That's ok.
- 对不起，泰迪，但这是事实。
- 没关系。
That is just wildly inappropriate.
这只是非常地时机不恰当。
And yet... I'm really glad you're here.
All you guys. Even you Alan.
可是...我真的很高兴你们在这里??
你们所有。即使是你 艾伦。
It means a lot that you made the trip.
Thank you.
这让这趟旅行意义非凡。谢谢。
- Wouldn't have missed it buddy.
- Great!
- 我们不会忘的，这哥们。
- 太好了！
Now. Can we have our one fucking beer, dad?
现在。我们可以再喝一轮我们他妈的啤酒，爸爸？
Alright. Toast! C'mon stand up guys.
好吧。乾杯！拜托你们站起来。
Come over here, Alan!
到这里来，艾伦！
To Lauren and Stu!
为了萝拉和史都！
- You did it, buddy.
- Sure did.
- 你做到了，夥计。
- 确实这样做了。
Cheers!
乾杯
What the hell...
搞甚麽 ...
What?
什麽？
Phil...
菲尔 ...
I think it happened again.
我们又出包了...
- Alan, what the fuck did you do?
- I didn't do anything. I swear to god.
- 艾伦，你他妈又做了什麽？
- 我发誓我没有做任何事情。
Your hair is gone.
你的毛剃光了。
No, no... up.
不，头上的头发。
Where the fuck are we?
我们他妈的在哪？
Phil, I'm scared.
菲尔，我好怕。
Stu, c'mon get up! We got a situation.
史都，拜托起床！我们现在有状况。
- Oh, holy shit!
- Where are we?
- 哦，妈的...
- 我们在哪？
- Oh my god, Alan. Your head.
- No your head!
- 噢，我的上帝，艾伦。你的头。
- 不 是你的头吧！
- Is it bald?
- Stu, you're gonna freak out, but it's gonna be ok.
- 是秃头？
- 史都，你会抓狂，但它会好的。
- Why? Was it my teeth?
- Nope, it's not your teeth.
- 为什麽？因为我的牙齿？
- 不，不是你的牙齿。
- Are you sure?
- Yep.
- 你确定吗？
- 没错。
Can you see the bottom?
你能看到下面吗？
Oh my god! What the fu...ck
天哪！这是什麽...
at's good. Why don't you try to wash it off.
Th很好看。你为什麽不尝试把它洗掉。
It's not coming off. This is a real tattoo!
洗不掉。这是一个真正的纹身！
- Alan, what did you do! Did you Roofie me?
- I didn't do anything!
- 艾伦，你做了什麽！你对我下药了吗？
- 我没有做任何事情！
Stu, he swore to god!
史都，他对上帝发誓！
What happened?
发生了什麽事？
Get it off of me!
把从我身上弄掉！
- What the hell?
- It's a monkey.
- 这是什麽鬼东西？
- 这是一只猴子。
What a cute little mask. Hi little monkey.
多麽可爱的小面具。嗨，小猴子。
Alan...
艾伦 ...
Phone! Alan, go find the phone!
手机！艾伦，去找电话！
I got it!
我找到了！
- Doug, where the hell are you?
- I'm at breakfast. By the pool.
- 道格，你到底在哪里？
- 我在吃早餐。在泳池边。
- You guys coming down or what?
- Oh Jesus. Thank god. Doug's fine.
- 你们要下来 还是怎麽样？
- 哦耶稣。感谢上帝。 道格没事。
- Stu, Doug's fine. He's at the resort.
- Why aren't we at the resort.
- 史都，道格没事。他在度假村。
- 为什麽我们不在度假村。
What's going on? Where are you guys?
这是怎麽回事？你们在哪里？
I do not know, man! We woke up
in some shit hole room in some city.
我不知道，老兄！我们醒在某个城市的某个房间里。
- Oh god. What city?
- I don't know, Doug!
- 哦，上帝。哪个城市？
- 我不知道，道格！
Fuckin Asia-town.
该死的亚洲城市。
- I do not know, I told you.
- Where are we?
- 我不知道，我跟你说。
- 我们在哪儿？
- Hey Stu.
- What?
- 嘿 史都。
- 什麽？
Check this out.
看一下这个。
Ever seen anything like this?
曾经见过像这样吗？
- What is that?
- Careful. Might be a spiders nest.
- 那是什麽？
- 当心。可能是一个蜘蛛巢。
I've tangled with those before.
我之前有碰过。
I don't get it man. We each had one beer
last night, right? I mean you too!
我不明白。我们昨晚每个人都有一瓶啤酒，对不对？我的意思是你也是！
- Yeah but I left early, remember?
- I don't remember shit!
- 是的，但是我离开得比较早，记得吗？
- 我什麽都不记得！
Tracy wasn't feeling well. She came
特雷西不舒服。她下来找我。wn to get me.
- Wait and second. Is Teddy with you guys?
- Teddy? What? What are you talking about?
- 等一下。泰迪跟你们在一起吗？
- 泰迪？什麽？你在说些什麽？
He wasn't in his room. They've been
looking for him all morning.
他没有在自己的房间。他们整个上午都在找他。
- Teddy went to Stanford, right?
- Yeah. Why?
- 泰迪去斯坦福大学读书，对不对？
- 是啊。为什麽呢？
Fuck!
草
- I just found his finger!
- What?
- 我刚发现他的手指！
- 什麽？
- I just found his fucking finger, Doug!
- Phil, what is going on?
- 我刚发现他的他妈的手指，道格！
- 菲尔，到底是怎麽回事？
Alright. Alright, alright... this is
what we're gonna do.
好吧。好吧，好吧...这是我们要做的。
You tell the girls that we woke up early and went
on a fishing trip, ok. And that's where we are.
你告诉女孩们，我们早早起床去钓鱼，好吗。而那是我们去的地方。
- Right.
- Right, stay by the phone!
- 好。
- 好，留在电话旁
Shit!
妈的！
Uh, we got a little bit of a problem.
嗯，我们发现了一点点小问题。
What is that?
那是什麽？
We don't know.
我们不知道。
- Is it a worm?
- It's a mushroom.
- 那是蠕虫吗？
- 这是一个蘑菇。
Yeah, shiitake.
是啊，香菇。
Monkey, taste it! Is it shiitake?
猴子，吧！它是香菇吗？
- He can't understand you.
- He just did.
- 无法理解你。
- 刚刚做了。
- Why is he pulling on it?
- He's probably hungry.
- 为什麽去拉它？
- 可能饿了。
Wait a second. Is that...
等一下。是...
What the fuck man. Tell that gay monkey
to leave my shit alone.
什麽他妈。告诉那同志猴子 滚我远一点。
Chow?
老周？
You're fucking crazy.
你他妈的疯了。
It's so fucking light in here!
Alan, grab me my sunglasses!
这里太他妈的亮了！
艾伦，拿我的太阳镜过来！
- It's great to see you, Leslie!
- Nice to see you too my little popo.
- 很高兴地看到你，老周！
- 很高兴见到你 我的小波波。
Chow, what the fuck are you doing here?
老周，你他妈在这里干嘛？
Alan called me a few days ago and
invited me to the wedding.
艾伦几天前打电话给我 邀请我来参加婚礼。
- Excuse me?
- What, he's my plus one.
- 什麽？
- 什麽，他是我的伴。
You don't have plus one. It's $200 a plate.
您没有伴。这要花200美元一趟。
Guys, guys. Just focus, ok.
Chow, what happened?
夥计们，夥计们。专心点，好吗。
老周，发生什麽事了？
You guys texted me, said you're fucked
up and looking to party.
你们传简讯给我，说你们玩疯了然後要开个派对。
I picked you up on my boat and I brought
you here to Bangkok.
我带你们上我的船 带你们来曼谷。
But we had a sick night, bitches!
我们昨晚超变态的，逊咖们！
Wait a second Chow,  we're in Bangkok?
等等，我们在曼谷？
Holler, city of squalor.
哈啦，淫乱之都。
- Do you know how I got this tattoo?
- Uh, yeah from a fucking tattoo guy!
- 你知道我是怎麽得到这个纹身？
- 嗯，是从一个他妈的帮人纹身的家夥！
Come on Stu, use that big Jewish brain.
来吧 史都，用用你那犹太人的大脑。
What's the monkey holding?
那猴子拿的是什麽？
- That's a finger!
- Stu, I got some bad news.
- 那是一个手指！
- 史都，我有一些坏消息。
Teddy was with us last night.
That's his finger.
泰迪昨晚与我们在一起。这是他的手指
- Teddy's dead?
- Teddy's not dead! He partied with us all night!
- 泰迪死了吗？
- 泰迪没有死！他整晚与我们一同欢乐！
- Well then where is he?
- Don't you remember anything?
- 那麽他在哪儿？
- 你不记得吗？
- No!
- No, nothing, Chow.
- 不！
- 不，什麽都不记得，老周。
Ok I explain it all, ok?
好，我解释这一切，好吗？
Just let me do one bump, get my head straight.
Come to papa.
就让我吸一口，让我的头清醒。过来爸爸这里。
That's a big...
这是一个大...
You ready for craziest fucking story ever...
你准备好听到有史以来最疯狂的故事...他妈的
Chow!
老周！
Hey Chow, you okay?
老周 嘿，你没事吧？
You gotta be kidding me.
你肯定在开玩笑吧。
Fuck, he's dead!
日，他死了！
- Help!
- Stu!
- 救人喔！
- 史都！
- Help!
- Stu, shut up!
- 救人喔！
- 史都，闭嘴！
- Call an ambulance!
- Shut up! He's dead!
- 呼叫救护车！
- 闭嘴！他死了！
Look if someone comes and finds a dead
body and a pile of cocaine...
如果有人看到，发现一具铺搴鸵欢芽煽ㄒ...
We're gonna spend the rest of our fucking
lives in a Thai prison.
我们的下半辈子要留在泰国的监狱。
Alan! Please don't cry!
艾伦！请不要哭泣！
Alright. Alright. I just need a second to
figure this out.
好吧。好吧。我只需要一秒钟来想清楚。
ICE MACHINE LOCATED ON 15TH FLOOR.
制冰机位於 15楼。
Look, this is the worst idea, ever.
看，这是最糟糕的主意。
What the fuck is this place?
这是他妈的什麽地方？
Bangkok is the capital of Thailand. Its
population is 12 million people...
曼谷是泰国的首都?Ｆ淙丝谑?12亿人...
Alan, will you help!
艾伦，你帮帮忙！
- The elevator!
- I'll get the button!
- 电梯！
- 我去按按钮！
- What the fuck is the deal with this monkey?
- That monkey gets it!
- 要怎麽处理这只他妈的猴子？
- 那只猴子就要遭殃了！
- Come on!
- Fuck no!
- 来吧！
- 他妈的，不！
The powers out. We gotta take the stairs.
停电了。我们得走楼梯。
- Oh fuck!
- Come on!
- 哦，他妈的！
- 来吧！
Here it is!
在这里！
Feet first. I've done this before.
脚先。我以前已经这样做过了。
Careful!
小心！
- Stu!
- What?
- 史都！
- 什麽？
- We still have to find Teddy!
- Oh god.
- 我们仍然必须找到泰迪！
- 哦，上帝。
The roof!
屋顶！
Teddy!
- You guys see him?
- No!
- 你们看到他吗？
- 木有！
He's not here.
他不在这里。
I can't believe this is happening again.
我不敢相信这又再次发生。
Ok, look. We'll handle this. You get
back there.
好，好吧。我们可以处理的。你回去那里。
You tell them that Alan and I got drunk
with him, we're still partying.
你告诉他们，艾伦和我喝醉 跟他在一起，我们仍然庆祝。
- You gotta go get married!
- No! Not going back without Teddy!
- 你必须去结婚吧！
- 不！没有泰迪我不回去！
He's Lauren's little brother. He's lost,
he's injured.
他是萝拉的弟弟。他失踪了，他受伤了。
If I fuck this up, I lose everything.
如果我搞砸了，我将失去了一切。
Ok.
好的。
Alright.
好吧。
- Alan, check your pockets!
- What?
- 艾伦，检查你的口袋！
- 什麽？
You know the drill. C'mon there might
be clues.
你知道该怎麽做。来吧，有可能有线索。
- Check your phones! Numbers, texts.
- That's a good idea!
- 检查你的手机！电话号码，简讯。
- 这是个好主意！
- I got nothing. Fuck!
- I got an text from Chow.
- 我什麽都没有。他妈的！
- 我有一个老周寄的简讯。
- What time?
- Uh, 10 o'clock last night.
- 什麽时候？
- 嗯，昨晚10点。
- What's it say?
- "On my way, Niggahs"
- 说什麽？
- 「上路了，Niggahs」
Oh, Niggahs... ok... hip hop.
哦，Niggahs ...好的...嘻哈。
We are so... fucked!
我们彻底的...完了！
Hey Phil! Look who's back!
嘿 菲尔！看看谁回来了！
We gotta get you out of the sun. You're
too hot.
我们得让你防晒了。你太热了。
Phil, I really think we should go to
the American Consulate.
菲尔，我真的觉得我们应该去美国领事馆。
For what? To report a dead body we shoved
into an ice machine?
为了什麽？要报告一具铺澹我们推到制冰机中？
What are we gonna do? Keep walking around
in circles? Cause that's real productive.
我们要怎麽办？继续闲晃吗？因为那可真正的有用。
You know I'm trying to figure this thing
out here and your attitude is not helping.
你知道我在想清楚这件事情，你的态度并没有帮助。
I'm sorry. It's a 100 degrees and we
don't have a plan.
我很抱歉。现在已经100度F，而我们没有一个计划。
And all we've done is buy him hats and sodas.
而我们所做的就是给他买帽子和苏打水。
-What, it's a bag of Fanta!
- Alright, what do you want to do, Stu?
-什麽，这是一个袋子芬达！
- 好吧，你想要怎麽做，史都？
I don't know!
我不知道！
Well then stop yelling at me like it's my fuckin fault.
那麽就别对我叫 好像这是我他妈的错。
It is your fault!
这是你的错！
All I wanted was a bachelor brunch.
我想要的只是一个单身汉早午餐。
Shit! Shut up! It's Doug! Talk to me!
妈的！闭嘴！是道格！跟我说话！
I just got off the phone with Bangkok PD.
They've got him. He's ok.
我刚刚跟曼谷警察联络。他们已经找到他。他没事。
Oh thank god! Doug found him.
哦，感谢上帝！道格找到了他了。
- What happened?
- He got arrested.
- 发生了什麽？
- 他被逮捕了。
- Arrested? For what?
- Disorderly conduct.
- 被捕了？为什麽？
- 行为不检。
- Seriously?
- Yeah! He's ok though.
- 真的吗？
- 是啊！不过他没事。
They'll release him to you. No questions
asked. No one has to know.
他们会释放他给你。没有问问题。也没有人知道。
He's at the Ratra Wang police station.
他在Ratra王派出所。
Ok. I'll call you when we get there.
好的。我会打电话给你，当我们到达那里。
Teddy's in jail, but he's fine. We
gotta get a cab.
泰迪在监狱里，但他没事。我们得叫台计程车
- Ok!
- Alright!
- 好吧！
- Yes, I have his paperwork here.
- Okay.
- 是的，我这里有他的文件纪录。
- 好。
- He has been treated.
- Sounds good.
- 已经开始处理了。
- 听起来不错。
We're good. They've processed him for
release.
我们很好。他们已经为他处理释放事宜
They put him in the drunk tank. He's fine.
他们把他放在酒醉室里。他没事。
Sixteen years old and spent a night in
jail. Can you imagine?
十六岁，待在监狱一晚上。你能想像吗？
Haha! We love to party.
哈哈！我们热爱派对。
Here we go!
我们走！
- Wait who's this fuckin guy?
- Teddy Sisay.
- 等等 该死的家夥是谁？
- 泰迪Sisay。
No, no, no, no. That's the wrong guy! Sir!
不，不，不，不。这是错误的家夥！先生！
Excuse me.. I'm sorry. Officer. You brought
the wrong guy. That's not Teddy!
对不起..我很抱歉。警官。你放错人了。这不是泰迪！
Of course it is!
We have his ID's and everything!
当然是！
我们有他的ID和一切！
These were in his pocket
when we made the arrest.
当我们逮捕他时 这些都是在他的口袋里。
They were in his pocket?
在他的口袋里？
Excuse me, sir! How did you get this stuff?
对不起，先生！你是怎麽得到这个东西？
Hello?
哈罗？
Teddy doesn't speak. We tried English,
Thai, Chinese... Nothing.
泰迪无法说话。我们尝试了英语，泰文，中文 ...什麽也没用。
Let me ask you something.
让我问问你。
Does he look like he works out at Bally
Total Fitness in Palo Alto, California?
他看起来有像是在加州Palo Alto的Bally完全健身房运动的人吗？
Look. We arrest a lot of people. We cannot
analyze everything.
看看。我们逮捕了很多人。我们无法分析每件事。
- What do you expect us to do with this guy?
- Not my problem!
- 你希望我们如何处理这家夥？
- 这不是我的问题！
Hey guys, I think he knows us. Hi. Hello.
嘿 家夥，我觉得他应该认识我们。你好。你好。
You know where our friend is, Teddy?
He's missing!
你知道我们的朋友在哪里吗，泰迪？他失踪了！
- Stu, forget it. The guys worthless.
- He knows something!
- 史都，算了吧。这些家夥毫无用处。
- 他知道些什麽！
He's wearing Teddy's sweatshirt.
他穿着泰迪的运动衫。
Maybe he just doesn't understand. I'll
act it out. Yeah, like charades. Watch.
也许他只是不能理解。我会想出办法。是啊，就像猜哑谜。看着。
- Two words.
- Is it a movie?
- 两个单字。
- 是电影吗？
This is not for you, Alan!
这不是给你看的，艾伦！
- American teenager... in Asia.
- Karate Kid, with Jaden Smith.
- 美国少年...在亚洲。
- 空手道小子，与杰登史密斯。
It's easy cause you're talking to him.
这很容易 因为你在对他说话。
Stu, it's a waste of time! Just leave
this fucking guy here.
史都，这是浪费时间！把这家夥他妈的留在这里。
Here's something. There are 500 thousand
monks living in Thailand.
这里有什麽。在泰国有五十万个僧侣。
It is not uncommon for some monks to take
a vow of silence, at the age of eight.
一些僧侣发沉默愿则非少见的，在八岁时。
There you go.
算了吧。
- Anything else in that envelope?
- Nah, it's empty.
- 有任何东西在外套里？
- 不，它是空的。
Woah, hang on. A drink card from White
Lion bar in Bangkok?
哇，等等。有一张曼谷的白狮酒吧的白喝卡？
Worth a shot.
值得一试。
Jesus christ! Is this the right street?
耶稣基督！这是正确的路吗？
That's what it says.
它是这麽说。
- Whoa! This is the White Lion!
- What the fuck happened here?
- 哇！这就是白狮！
- 这里是他妈的怎麽一回事？
Holy shit!
真他妈的！
(yelling in Thai)
（喊叫）
- Let's...
- We should probably...
- 让我们 ...
- 我们也许应该
That's ok.
没关系。
What the fuck is going on here?
他妈的是怎麽回事？
- Whoa, guys. Check it out!
- Holy shit! Stu, look!
- 哇，夥计们。来看看吧！
- 狗屎！史都，看！
That's my face. Go, go go!
Nice work, Alan!
这是我的脸。走吧，进去进去！干的好，艾伦！
- Hello?
- Be with you in a minute!
- 哈罗？
- 等我一分钟！
- Excuse me.
- Oh, look who it is!
- 对不起。
- 哦，看看这是谁！
- So what do ya think?
- What, I'm sorry?
- 那麽你觉得如何？
- 什麽，对不起？
- The tattoo. You love it?
- Uh, no. Actually, I hate it.
- 那个纹身。你喜欢它吗？
- 嗯，没有。其实，我讨厌它
- No refunds. Get the fuck out!
- Wait a second!
- 不退款。给我滚出去！
- 等一下！
Read the sign!
看清楚标示??！
NO REFUNDS. GET THE FUCK OUT OF HERE.
没有退款。他妈的给我离开这里。
We don't want any refunds. We just have
a couple of questions.
我们没有要退款。我们只是要问一些问题。
We're trying to figure out what went
down last night.
我们正试图找出昨晚发生了什麽。
What went down? Take a look at what you
did outside. Half the neighborhood went down.
发生了什麽？去外面看看你们做的。附近几乎一半都毁了。
- We did that?
- You don't remember getting into a bar fight at the White Lion?
- 我们做的？
- 你不记得，在白狮酒吧参与了一场打斗？
- Starting a full on fuckin riot?
- Sir, we don't remember anything.
- 引发一场完整的他妈的暴动？
- 先生，我们什麽都不记得。
Oh boy...
哦，孩子...
Check this out!
看一下这个！
Oh shit!
哦，妈呀！
Fuck the Police!
草那警察
There's Teddy! He was with us!
还有泰迪！他和我们在一起！
Jesus christ!
天呐！
That's when the cops arrived and started
cracking skulls.
这是当员警抵达，并开始打人时。
I took you guys and hid you in the
shop here.
我把你们藏在店里。
Then you decided to get a tattoo.
You cried like a little bitch.
然後你决定要一个纹身。
你哭得像一个小婊子。
This kid is fucking nine years old. He's
got balls twice your size.
这小子是他妈的九岁。他的蛋蛋是你的两倍。
- Show him your balls, Nao!
- No, no, no. That's ok.
- 给他看你的蛋，Nao！
- 不，不，不。没关系。
Listen, we're looking for our friend Teddy.
Have you seen him?
听着，我们正在寻找我们的朋友泰迪。
你见过他吗？
Not since last night. Why? What happened?
昨晚之後没有。为什麽呢？发生了什麽事？
Yeah, I'm supposed to marry his sister
tomorrow and we kinda lost him.
是啊，我明天应该娶他的姐姐，我们好像找不到他。
- Oh well. Then fuck it!
- What do you mean, fuck it?
- 哦。好 那麽他妈的吧！
- 你是什麽意思，他妈的吧？
Bangkok has him now and she'll never
let him go.
曼谷拥有他了 她永远不会让他走。
- You hear that, huh? Is this what you
wanted? You happy now?
- 你听到了吧？这就是你希望的吗？你高兴了吗？
You're wasting your time. These monks
take their vow shit seriously.
你在浪费你的时间。这些僧侣非常认真的守誓言。
Look at this. That's the sign of the Chang
Mai Monastery, just outside of town.
看看这个。这是张麦寺的符号，就在城市外面。
Maybe somebody over there can get him
to talk.
也许那里有人可以让他说话。
- Ok, can we just go over this one
more time? You got the beer from...
- 好吧，我们可以过的了这一关吗？你拿了啤酒从...
- The hotel bar. They gave me a sealed case.
- Right.
- 酒店的酒吧。他们给了我一箱没开过的。
- 对。
- But, who gave it to you?
- The bartender.
- 但是，是谁拿给你的？
- 调酒师
And then you brought em out and
I  opened them.
然後你带出来 我再打开它们。
Yeah and Doug had one and he was fine
so it's not the beer.
是啊 而且道格也喝了 所以问题不是因为啤酒。
- So what the hell happened?
- I have no idea!
- 那麽到底发生了什麽事？
- 我不知道！
Hey guys. Check it out. He's got a
Chinese boner.
嘿，夥计们。看一下。他有一根大拧
Alan, come on! Cut it out!
艾伦，拜托！ 停止吧！
- That is so wrong!
- Don't stop monkey, keep doing it.
- 这是错误的！
- 不要停 ?镒樱^续做下去。
When a monkey nibbles on a penis
it's funny in any language!
当猴子玩大m时，比甚麽都好笑
Keep doing it!
继续做下去！
Alright, thank you!
好吧，谢谢你！
Bye Shannon! Bye Little Wayne!
再见 香！再见 小韦恩！
Wow! So beautiful!
哇！太美了！
What is this, a PF Chang's?
这是什麽，一家 PF Chang中菜馆？
Ah, they're meditating.
啊，他们在打坐。
- Such a peaceful people!
- Yeah.
- 好一个爱好和平的人民！
- 是啊。
- Knock, knock! Hello!
- Alan! Show some respect!
- 敲敲门，敲敲门！您好！
- 艾伦！表现出一定的尊重！
- Don't get up guys.
- We brought one of your guys back.
- 别起来 各位。
- 我们把你们的一个家夥带回来。
He's really funny. He's really nice
and cool.
他真的很有趣。他的真不错 也很酷。
Hi, how you doing. You the one in charge?
嗨，你好。你就是负责人？
- Excuse me... ow... Wait!
- Stop it! Calm down!
- 对不起...哇 ...等等！
- 住手！冷静下来！
Hold on. It's because we're talking.
HOD住。那是因为我们在交谈。
God damn it! Oh! Stop!
他妈的！哦！住手！
Wait it's me!
等等 是我！
Oh I get it.
噢，我明白了。
No talk! No talk! Shh.. Ok...
不说话！不说话！嘘 ..好了...
Ok.
好的。
Late last night, you climbed the walls
of our monastery.
昨天深夜，你爬上我们的寺院的墙。
Shouting out questions about love, marriage
and the meaning of life.
喊着关於爱情，婚姻和生命意义的问题。
Poor brother Han was meditating alone
in the garden.
可怜的寒兄弟独自在花园里打坐。
- And you took him.
- Oh my god!
- 然後你带走他。
- 噢，我的上帝！
- We kidnapped a monk.
- We live an alternative life style.
- 我们绑架了一名僧人。
- 我们以一种另类方式生活。
We are so sorry about that, but we weren't
ourselves last night.
我们很遗憾，但我们昨晚已经不受控制了。
Yep, things kinda spun outta control a little
bit. But there's a boy who's missing and hurt.
是的，事情有点失控 。但是有一个男孩失踪并受伤了。
Can you find out if he knows where our
friend is?
你能否能找出讯息 如果他知道我们的朋友在哪？
Brother Han took a vow of silence many
years ago.
寒兄弟多年前发了沈默誓。
It would be useless to try.
这将是无用的尝试。
Well maybe he can write down what happened,
on a piece of paper?
嗯，也许他可以写下发生了什麽事？
Actually Phil, that would be cheating.
Isn't that right, Grand Wizard.
事实上 菲尔，这将是作弊。是不是啊，大导师。
- Alan!
- I'm afraid fatty is right.
- 艾伦！
- 恐怕胖兄弟是对的。
See?... What?
听到了吗？...什麽？
None of us will ever know what brother
Han knows.
我们永远不会知道寒兄弟知道的事。
Oh, alright. Well, so much for holy people.
Bunch of bald assholes. C'mon, let's go.
哦，好吧。那麽，跟圣民说了这麽多。
这帮王八蛋秃。来吧，我们走吧。
Hey you know what! FYI! You may want to
put some signs up that say no talking...
嘿，你知道吗！仅供参考！您可能要指出一些徵兆 然後说不准说话 ...
- ...before you unleash your dragon.
- Yeah, that was a little rough.
- ...在你释放你的龙之前。
- 是啊，那是有点粗鲁。
And "your welcome" for bringing him
back safe.
还有「不客气」把他平安带回来。
- You know we found him in the drunk tank.
- Yeah well we did take him in the first place.
- 你知道，我们载酒醉室发现他。
- 是啊，我们也把他从这里带走。
- C'mon guys, let's go.
- Wait!
- 来吧，夥计们，我们走吧。
- 等等！
The Buddha teach, every memory lives
somewhere deep within.
佛陀教导我们，每一个的记忆都在内心深处的某个地方。
Perhaps you should bring your question
to the Garden of Meditation.
也许你应该把你的问题带去沉思花园。
- Did you understand a word he just said?
- Yeah, yeah. About two thirds.
- 你了解你刚才说的每个字吗？
- 是啊，是啊。大约理解三分之二。
He said something about the Garden of
Meditation?
他说了一些关於沉思花园的
No, he said he's farting because of
his medication.
不，他说他放屁，因为他服药。
I get that.
我明白了。
It's a waste of time. I don't remember
anything. Do you?
这是在浪费时间。我什麽都不记得。你呢？
No. I got nothing. Alan?
不，我也是。艾伦？
Alan!
艾伦！
"Every memory lives somewhere deep within"
「每一个的记忆都在内心深处的某个地方」
- Sweetie.
- What?
- 亲爱的。
- 什麽？
You have visitors.
你有客人。
- Hey, Alan!
- Hey, guys!
- 嘿，艾伦！
- 嗨，哥们！
- 嗨，菲尔。
- 嗨，老兄！
Stu would like to invite you to his wedding.
史都想邀请你参加他的婚礼。
- Is this true, Stuart?
- Yeah, why not. It'll be fun.
- 真的吗，史都尔特？
- 是啊，为什麽不呢。这会有趣的。
Fuck!
他妈的！
- For Lauren and Stu!
- Cheers!
- 敬萝拉和史都！
- 乾杯！
- Chow!
- We had a sick night bitches!
- 老周！
- 我们昨晚超变态的，逊咖们！！
Alan, what the fuck!
艾伦，这是什麽！
Is that person coming to the wedding?
- There is no wolfpack.
- Alan, Alan, don't do that!
- 没有狼群。
- 艾伦，艾伦，别那麽做！
And finally...
最後 ...
The three best friends anyone could have.
每个人可以拥有三个最好的朋友。
Fuck the Police!
他妈的警察
I know where to go.
我知道该去哪里。
- What do you think, Alan?
- This is the place.
- 你觉得，艾伦？
- 这是一个地方。
C'mon. Let's go.
来吧。我们走吧。
I don't remember any of this!
我不记得这里的任何事！
- Yeah Alan, you sure this is the place?
- Yeah, pretty sure.
- 是呀 艾伦，你确定这个地方？
- 是的，非常肯定。
Rose! Harmony!
玫瑰！和谐
Is he coming or what? I've been waiting
all day for him.
他要来还是怎样？我整天一直在等待他。
- I'm sorry. Waiting for who?
- Chow, that dick ass fuck!
- 我很抱歉。等待谁？
- 老周，这他妈的屁股家夥！
- Why? What's wrong?
- Nothings wrong.
- 为什麽？这是怎?N回事？
- 没事。
Ok, good. Look at this. Look what I
bring for him. Check it out, huh.
好，好。看看这个。看看我带来的。检查看看，呵呵。
- No, no!
- $ 6,000 American.
- 不，不！
- $ 6,000元 美元。
Wow looks so real!
哇 看起来很像真的！
Sorry!
对不起！
- Alan, what the fuck!
- It's ok. The gun, it's very sensitive.
- 艾伦，怎麽回事！
- 没关系。这枪，这是非常敏感。
Everybody ok?
大家都好吗？
Ok, then get the fuck back to work!
Come on. Music, please!
好了，回去工作！来吧。放音乐，请！
Where is my 6,000 dollars?
那是我6000美元吗？
6,000? No, no, no. This is Chow's deal. We
got nothing to do with that.
6000？不，不，不。这是老周的交易。我们
跟这一点关系也没有。
Un-fucking believable.
他妈的难以置信。
This guy, if he backs out again, the
shits gonna catch up with him.
这家夥，如果敢再回来，可有的他好受的。
He's made a lot of enemies in this town,
and now they're gonna be your enemies.
他在这城市树立很多的敌人，
而现在他们会成为你们的敌人。
That's not fair!
这不公平！
Ok listen. We're just looking for a
little kid.
听好了。我们只是寻找一个小孩。
- 2,000 dollars.
- What!
- 2,000美元。
- 什麽！
I don't know, maybe more. How young you
want this kid to be?
我不知道，也许要更多。你希望这小子多年轻呢？
No, no! Sorry, you misunderstood. We're
looking for our friend... 16 years old.
不，不！对不起，你误会了。我们寻找我们的朋友... 16岁。
- Teddy.
- Teddy?
- 泰迪。
- 泰迪？
- Yeah he was here with you guys last night.
- He was?
- 他昨晚跟你们在这里。
- 他什麽？
Do you know if he left with us?
你知不知道，他有没有离开我们呢？
I don't know. You were in the corner all
night with Kimmy.
我不知道。你们整夜和Kimmy待在角落。
- I didn't see you leave.
- Kimmy?
- 我没有看到你们离开。
- Kimmy？
- Is she here?
- Yes, she's in the back. She just came for her shit.
- 她在这里吗？
- 是的，她在後面。她刚刚到了，为了她那狗屎。
Go and talk to her.
去和她谈谈。
Alright, listen. I'm sorry about everything
that happened.
好吧，听着。我很抱歉发生的一切。
Listen to me, ok? Pay attention to what
I'm going to talk to you know.
听我说，好吗？注意我要和你谈谈的事 你应该知道。
When you see Chow, you tell him Samir
says "Hello".
当你看到老周，你告诉他萨米尔跟他说声「你好」。
Okay!
好吧！
But do it like that, ok! "Hello" like
threatening. Like, ironic.
但是是这样做，好吗！ 「你好」要像威胁。就像，具有讽刺意味。
- "Hellooo"
- Okay!
- 「你好~~~~」
- 好吧！
Go away! Go away!
走开！走开！
??
？？
Of course I remember him. He was buying
shots for everyone.
我当然记得他。他替每个人买酒。
Nice kid! His parents must be so proud.
好孩子！他的父母一定很自豪。
You have no idea.
你根本不知道。
Ok, so do you remember if he left with us?
好了，你还记得吗，他有离开我们吗？
Yeah, you were all leaving together, but
you almost forgot this one right here.
是啊，你们一起离去，但你几乎忘了这一个还在这里。
Right, super star?
没错，超级明星？
This one was following me around like a
little puppy dog. All night.
而他则像一只小小狗 整夜跟着我周围。
Saying he'd fallen in love with me. Asked
me to marry him.
他说，他会爱上我。要我嫁给他。
Classic Stu!
好经典 史都！
- We didn't get married, did we?
- Course not!
- 我们没有结婚，是吗？
- 当然不是！
We just had some fun in the Chardonnay room.
我们只是在霞多丽的房间有一些好玩的。
- What happens in the Chardonnay room?
- Let's just stay on task.
- 发生什麽是在霞多丽的房间里？
- 让我们专心找人。
I danced for him. He tickled me. We had sex.
我跳舞给他。他骚我痒。我们有性行为。
- Fuck!
- It's ok. You're not married yet.
- 靠！
- 这没关系。你还没有结婚。
- No big deal.
- It's cheating!
- 没什麽大不了的。
- 这是欺骗！
No offense to you. You're a lovely woman.
没有冒犯你。你是个可爱的女人。
It's a violation of my moral code.
但这是违背我的道德准则。
Don't be sad. Stu you loved it. You were
crying, saying how special it was.
不要伤心。史都 你喜欢它。你哭了，说明这是多麽特别。
- Wait! I'm sorry. He was crying?
- What a baby. He was crying.
- 等等！我很抱歉。他在哭吗？
- 你还小吗。他哭了。
You should have seen him. He was so
sexy. The way he moved around.
你应该有见过他。他是如此性感。他以这种方式移动。
I had to ask him to slow down so I didn't
drop my load too quick.
我要他慢下来，我才不会太快释放。
- Load? What load?
- Oh, you know... My sperms.
- 释放？释放什麽？
- 哦，你知道...我的精子。
I think your English is off. You're talking
about my sperm!
我觉得你的英语是错的。你在说关於"我的精子"！
- Where would your sperm come from?
- From my balls!
- 你的精子是从哪里来的？
- 从我的球！
- Hold on! Back up!
- Wait... Are you...
- 等等！重来！
- 等等...你是...
Hey. You're in Bangkok, sweetie.
嘿。你是在曼谷Bangkok，亲爱的。
- There's a reason they don't call it "Bang-cunt".
- Oh!
- 所以有原因，他们不叫「曼Bang-cunt」。
-啊！
- Oh god!
- Wow.
- 哦，上帝！
- 哇。
I don't get it. Is this a magic show?
我不明白。这是一个魔术表演？
Come on, Stu, it was beautiful. We climaxed
at the same time.
来吧，史都，它是美丽的。我们在同一时间高潮。
How's that work?
怎麽做的？
Shoot my load into you. Shoot your load
on the floor.
把我的精子射向你。你的精子射到地板上。
- Ok!
- You ruined me. Ruined bottom.
- 好吧！
- 你毁了我。彻底毁灭。
Oh god!
哦，上帝！
- Stu! It's not the end of the world.
- Sorry, but I'm so confused.
- 史都！这不是世界末日。
- 对不起，但我很困惑。
I made love to a man... with boobies.
我跟一个男人做爱 ...他有胸部。
Listen. I promise you no ones ever gonna
find out about this.
听着。我答应你 没有任何人会知道这件事。
But we found out about it.
但是，我们知道了。
And then we forget. That's what we do!
那麽，我们要忘记。这就是我们要做的！
I do so much fucked up shit. And I just
forget about it.
我也做了许多狗屎事。而我就是忘掉它。
- Yeah?
- Yeah! Just forget! It goes away!
- 是吗？
- 是啊！忘了！它消失了！
That might be harder to go away, but in
time it'll happen.
可能很难遗忘，但在时间会让它发生的。
I certainly do. Just gonna forget about it.
我当然要这麽做。就这麽忘了吧。
- Never happened.
- Great!
- 从来没有发生过。
- 太好了！
Phone! Phone! Who is it? Answer!
手机！手机！是谁？快接！
Lauren's dad. He just reminded me...
萝拉的父亲。他只是提醒我...
- Answer it!
- I can't.
- 快接吧！
- 我不能。
What! He might know something about Teddy.
C'mon we still have a shot here.
什麽！他可能知道一些关於泰迪的事。
拜托，我们还在这里找人耶。
Get your head back into the fucking game, Stu!
让你的精神回来这他妈的游戏，史都！
Hello?
哈罗？
Who takes an all day fishing trip the
day before a wedding?
谁会在结婚前一天花一整天去钓鱼之旅？
- Yeah, I guess that is kinda stupid.
- Put Teddy on the phone.
- 是啊，我想这是有点笨。
- 要泰迪接电话。
- Teddy's seasick actually.
- Seasick?
- 泰迪实际上晕船了。
- 晕船吗？
- Teddy's been a Maritime cadet since he was nine.
- That's weird, cause he's puking everywhere.
- 泰迪从九岁起一直是海事军校学生。
- 这真奇怪，因为他吐的到处都是。
I'm gonna tell you something that you do
not know.
我要告诉你一些你不知道的事。
- I don't like you.
- Yeah,I knew that already.
- 我不喜欢你。
- 是啊，这我知道了。
If my daughter chooses you,
that's her problem.
如果我的女儿选择你，
这是她的问题。
This is ??.
Hey it's Phil Winnick!
这是什麽..嘿，我是菲尔温尼克！
Listen, I apologize. We've been reelin
in some crazy Marlin and I just wanna say...
听着，我道歉。我们已经钓到一些疯了的马林鱼，我只想说 ...
Phil!
- Jesus!
- Phil!
Fuck me!
干我！
- Give us back our monkey!
- What monkey? Get your own monkey!
- 把我们的猴子还回来！
- 什麽猴子？去找你们自己的猴子！
Come on, you asshole, the fucking monkey!
来吧，你混蛋，他妈的猴子！
Come on!
来吧！
Anytime, Alan. He's pointing a gun at us!
任何时候，艾伦。他用枪指着我们！
This is our monkey!
这是我们的猴子！
No one's getting shot over a fucking monkey!
没有人要因为一只他妈的猴子被射杀！
Hand him over, now!
把交过去，现在！
God, I've never given him no monkeys.
上帝，我不想把猴子给他。
No, no ...
不，不...
Hey Phil, check it out. He's got a banana
on his helmet. He's the real deal.
嘿 菲尔，看一下。他的头盔上有一个香蕉。他是真正的主人。
What the fuck's happening?
他妈的是怎麽回事？
Hold on! How did this happen? Do you
know where our friend is?
等等！这是怎麽回事？你知道我们的朋友在哪吗？
- Yeah. Sixteen years old. Asian kid.
- (says something in Russian?)
- 是啊。十六岁。亚洲孩子。
- （用俄罗斯语说了些话？）
No, I don't understand what you said! No, I
didn't understand!
不，我不明白你说的！不，我不明白！
What'd he say?
他说什麽？
He said fuck you and your questions!
他说，去他妈的你和你的问题！
- Oh, my arm!
- Philip, are you okay?
- 哦，我的手臂！
- 菲力浦，你没事吧？
Oh I got shot! Fuck! Fuck this!
哦，我被射杀！他妈的！他妈的这个！
It's alright, Phil! It's alright!
没关系，菲尔！没关系！
We'll figure this out and get the monkey
back, I promise.
我们会想出解决办法，并把猴子找回来，我保证。
Who gives a fuck about the monkey!
谁在乎他妈的猴子！
- What the fuck is going on?
- Stu, am I gonna be ok? You're a doctor.
- 现在要怎麽办？
- 史都，我该怎麽办？你是个医生。
I don't know, let me look!
我不知道，让我看看！
What?
什麽？
Don't look at it!
不要看它！
Stuart Price! Get your ass back over here!
史都华普林斯！回来这里啊！
- You got shot!
- I know!
- 你被射中了！
- 我知道！
- Whoa, you all right?
- Yeah, I'm ok.
- 哇，你没事吧？
- 是啊，我没事。
Actually, bullet just grazed my arm.
Eight stitches.
其实，子弹只是擦过我的胳膊。缝八针。
Only cost six dollars. How is that even
possible?
只花了六块钱。这是怎麽回事，这可能吗？
How's any of this even possible?
怎麽不可能？
If I was a foot to my left, Stu, I'd be dead.
如果我是往左边移一点，史都，我就死了。
What are we gonna do?
我们要怎麽办？
I'm sorry guys. This wasn't part of the plan.
对不起 哥们。这不是计划的一部分。
- What plan, Alan?
- I've said too much already.
- 什麽计划，艾伦？
- 我已经说太多了。
Alan! What plan?
艾伦！什麽计划？
- It's all Teddy's fault.
- What are you talking about, Alan?
- 这都是泰迪的错。
- 你在说什麽，艾伦？
Why is he even here? He's not part of
the wolf pack!
他为什麽要来在这里？他不属於狼群！
- Alan, what did you do?
- It's not my fault!
- 艾伦，你又做什麽了？
- 这不是我的错！
Teddy shouldn't have been sharing from his bag.
泰迪不应该分享他的东西。
- What bag?
- The marshmallows.
- 什麽东西呢？
- 棉花糖。
I had a separate bag just for Teddy.
我有一包只为泰迪准备的。
But it was dark and it was hard to keep
track.
但那时很黑，它是很难保持注意。
And then, you almost sat on em. I couldn't
tell which was which.
然後，你们几乎坐好了。我不能
知道哪个是哪个。
- It was mayhem!
- What did you do to the marshmallows, Alan?
- 那时很混乱！
- 你对棉花糖做了什麽，艾伦？
Alan, what did you do?
艾伦，你做了什麽？
Isn't it obvious?
这不是很明显吗？
I spiked them with muscle relaxers. And
plus my ADHD medication.
我掺入肌肉松弛剂。和我的ADHD药物。
- What?
- You drugged us again?!
- 什麽？
- 你又对我们下迷药？！
Not you! I just wanted to knock out Teddy for a
little while so we could finally enjoy the weekend.
不是要对你们！我只是想搞掉泰迪一会儿，我们才可以享受周末。
Enjoy the weekend? Alan, you told me that
you didn't do anything!
享受周末？艾伦，你告诉我，你什麽也没做！
Alan, you swore to god!
艾伦，你对上帝发誓的！
I just wanted things to stay the same.
我只是希望事情保持不变。
Like at my face! You ruined my life!
像我的脸一样！你毁了我的一生！
You're not my friend!
你不是我的朋友！
Don't say that, Phil! You're serious?
Even in America?
别那麽说，菲尔！你是认真的？即使在美国也一样
- Yes!
- Oh God! Don't say that, Phil!
- 是的！
- 哦，上帝！别那麽说，菲尔！
- Don't start crying, Alan!
- You're the bearded devil!
- 不要开始哭，艾伦！
- 你是胡子恶魔！
You liked it! You smiled at me when I
handed you the bag with marshmallows.
你喜欢它！你对我微笑时，当我递棉花糖给你时。
Because I like marshmallows, you
fucking psycho!
因为我喜欢棉花糖，你这变态！
Hey! Whoa! Hold on!
嘿！哇！等等！
Enough!
够了！
- Why, Alan? Why?
- Stu!
- 为什麽，艾伦？为什麽呢？
- 史都！
Because we're the three best
friends, remember?
因为我们是三个最好朋友啊，还记得吗？
Remember?
还记得吗？
Stu, that's enough...
史都，够了...
Guys, we can't fall apart now. We gotta
stick together.
夥计们，我们不能土崩瓦解了。我们得粘在一起。
- Alan, what's that written on your belly?
- What? Huh?
- 艾伦，写在你的肚子上的是什麽？
- 什麽？咦？
Lebua Hotel, Saturday six pm.
莲花大酒店，周六下午六时。
- You write that?
- No!
- 你写的？
- 不！
Shit, that's in 20 minutes.
妈的，只剩20分钟。
What about England, Phil? Will we still
be friends there?
那麽英国呢，菲尔？在那里我们还会是朋友吗？
Alan, I already told you. It was in the heat of the
moment. We're still friends. All over the world.
艾伦，我已经告诉你了。现在是紧急状况。我们仍然是朋友。全世界都一样。
- Even Great Britain?
- Yeah.
- 即使是英国？
- 是啊。
What about you, Stu?
你呢，史都？
We'll see.
我们等着看看。
Gentlemen, follow me.
先生们，跟着我。
Here you go.
请过去。
Well. About time! Sit down.
嗯。很准时！坐下。
Come on, sit.
来吧，坐。
Wow, you guys look like shit.
哇，你们看起来像狗屎。
- Uh, do we know you?
- Hey!
- 嗯，我们认识你吗？
- 嘿！
Take off your fuckin hat. You're in a
restaurant for christs sake. C'mon.
脱掉你他妈的帽子。看在基督份上 你在一家餐厅耶。拜托。
Ok, listen. We have no clue what's
going on here.
好吧，听着。我们不清楚发生什麽事。
You know, they sell a Plum whiskey here,
it's fuckin unreal.
你知道，他们在这里卖李子威士忌，这绝对是他妈的假的。
Seriously, it will absolutely fuck you up! Oh, I'm
sorry. You guys already got fucked up, didn't you.
说真的，这绝对会整惨你们！哦，我抱歉。你们已经被搞惨了，?前伞?
- Uh, listen, I'm a little confused. How did you...
- You know what? I am a little fuckin confused!
- 嗯，听着，我有点糊涂了。你怎麽 ...
- 你知道吗？他妈的我也有点糊涂了！
Where's Chow? With the fuckin account
code and the fuckin password!
老周在哪里？还有他娘的帐户号码和密码！
We don't know anything about any codes. We're
just trying to find our friend.
我们不知道任何有关密码的事。我们只是想找到我们的朋友。
- Teddy?
- Yes! Teddy! Have you seen?
- 泰迪？
- 是的！泰迪！你见过？
Hmm, let's see...
嗯，让我们来看看...
There's Teddy!
泰迪在这里！
Holy shit! It's from last night.
真他妈的！这是昨天晚上拍的。
- Who are you?
- I'm a businessman.
- 你是谁？
- 我是一个商人。
And I've invested a large chunk of capital
in your friend Chow.
我在你的朋友老周处 投入了很大的一笔资金。
And in return, he was supposed to transfer
my profits electronically.
作为回报，他应该电子转帐给我的利润。
About five fuckin minutes ago.
约五分钟前。
So last night, we took Teddy as insurance.
所以，昨天晚上，我们带走了泰迪当作保险。
- Oh my god! Is he okay?
- Oh my god, I wasn't done talking.
- 噢，我的上帝！他还好吗？
- 哦，上帝，我还没有说完。
You tell Chow, that we are having breakfast
on the roof of this hotel...
你告诉老周，我们会在这家旅馆天台吃早饭...
...tomorrow morning at eight am.
...明天早上8时。
Or if he makes the transfer, you will
get Teddy.
或者，如果他转帐了，你会得到泰迪。
If not well then hey, you know...
it's Bangkok.
如果那时没有的话，你知道...这里是曼谷。
That's your cue to get the fuck out of here.
你们知道了就他妈的离开这里。
Hey, you know what? Leave the hat.
嘿，你知道吗？留下这顶帽子。
Alan leave the hat.
艾伦 留下帽子。
Atta boy.
好小子。
We're fucked! Chow's dead. What do we do now?
我们完了！老周死了。现在我们该怎麽办？
The guy doesn't give a shit about Chow, Stu.
This whole things about a fucking bank account.
那家夥才不管老周死活，史都。
整个事情都跟一个该死的银行帐户有关
Let's just go back to the hotel. We'll
search Chow's body.
让我们只是回到了酒店。我们将找回老周的尸体。
Hopefully the password's in his
wallet or something.
希望密码在他的钱包或哪里的。
- And what if it isn't?
- He's gonna kill Teddy.
- 而如果没有呢？
- 他会杀了泰迪。
Just relax. We have until 8am tomorrow
to figure it out.
别紧张。我们到明天上午8时前可以来弄明白。
First the monkey and now my hat. How
much worse can this day get.
首先是猴子，现在是我的帽子。这一天还可以怎麽个更糟糕。
Jesus christ!
上帝！
Well we're livin here in Alan town. And
he's drivin our lives into the ground.
嗯，我们生活在这里艾伦镇。而他却让我们的生活悲惨。
When we woke up we were wasted and drunk.
当我们醒来，我们既没用，也喝醉了。
Phil got shot. We got beaten by a monk.
菲尔被射杀。我们被和尚殴打。
I was happy, and my life was good.
我很高兴，我的生活是好的。
Getting married like a dentist should.
结婚应该像牙医。
Roasting marshmallows on a stick.
在棒子上烤棉花糖。
I got fucked in the ass... by a girl
with a dick.
我在屁股上性交...和一个有诺呐孩。
Oh yeah, remember that.
噢，记住这一点。
And we're livin in Alan town.
而且我们生活在艾伦镇。
There's water everywhere.
到处都是水。
Yeah it's cause it melted, Stu. The
fuckin powers out.
是的 因为冰融化了，史都。停电了。
With an inadequate electrical grid,
serving millions of people
这不足的电力供应着百万人口
Bangkok experiences 1500 power
outages per year.
曼谷一年会停电1500次。
Seriously, Alan. That's enough!
说真的，艾伦。这就够了！
Out of the way!
闪开！
We got it.
打开了。
Oh my god!
天哪！
Chow, calm down!
老周，冷静下来！
- You put the chill on me?
- No, no!
- 你们把我关在冰里吗？
- 不，不！
It's okay.
没关系。
Relax!
放松！
It's just us. Breathe!
这里只有我们。呼吸！
It was so cold.
好冷！
- We're gonna warm you up.
- I was so cold!
- 我们要温暖你。
- 我好冷！
- You did good, buddy. You did good.
- I did good.
- 你做得很好，夥计。你做得很好。
- 我做得很好。
Feelin better?
感觉好一点了吗？
- Alright, you warm enough?
- I don't know.
- 好吧，你够暖和了吗？
- 我不知道。
Come feel my bowels and tell me.
来感觉我的肠子的温度，再告诉我。
I've been locked in a fuckin ice box
all day!
我被锁在一个他妈的制冰机里 一整天！
Hey Alan, if you want my sunglasses...
嘿 艾伦，如果你想要我的太阳镜 ...
...just ask Chow. You don't have to kill me.
。。。去问老周。你没必要是我。
Chow, nobody killed you. You were already
dead. You didn't have a pulse.
老周，没人要杀你。你已经死了。你没有脉搏了。
Oh, you never do blow before?
哦，你从没做过心肺复苏吗？
Sometimes your heart stop... start
up again.
有时候你的心跳停止...然後又开始跳。
- Read a book!
- Look I'm sorry. We're having a bad day.
- 读读书！
- 我很抱歉。我们这一天很糟糕。
Oh, you're having a bad day! Did you die?
哦，你们这一天很糟糕！你们有死了吗？
- I got shot!
- But did you die?
- 我被射杀！
- 但你有死吗？
Chow, some guy told us that you got
a bank code or something...
老周，一些人告诉我们，你有银行号码或什麽 ...
...and if we don't bring it to him first
think in the morning...
...如果我们明天早上不把它带给他...
...he's gonna kill Teddy.
...他会杀了泰迪。
Who, Kingsley? He harmless. Don't worry.
I got the bank codes.
谁，金斯利？他是无害的。不要担心。
我有银行的号码。
Great! Alright, we gotta meet him at 8am.
Who is that fuckin guy, anyway?
太好了！好吧，我们得在上午8点见他。
这该死的家夥是谁，随便啦？
- An investor in my business.
- Yeah, what business is that?
- 投资我的生意的投资者。
- 是啊，什麽生意？
It's called "not your business" ok!
这就是所谓的「不甘你的事」好吗！
- Oh, where's the monkey?
- The monkey...
- 哦，猴子在哪里？
- 猴子...
Yeah I put the account number and
password in his vest. Where is he?
是的，我把帐号和密码放在的背心。在哪儿？
- Why would you do that?
- Safe keeping, pretty boy.
- 为什麽要这麽做？
- 为了保管安全，漂亮男孩。
I got a lotta heat on my ass. I got
FBI, Bangkok PD, Interpol, MSNBC...
很多人在找我。有联邦调查局，曼谷警察，FBI，MSNBC的...
That little monkey snorting coke with me
all night...
那个小猴子整夜跟我吸食毒品...
Jerkin me off while I watched Stu make
fuckin lady boy.
帮我手淫 当我看史都干他妈的女男孩时。
- He not going anywhere.
- We don't have the monkey, Chow.
- 哪儿也没去。
- 我们没有猴子，议员。
Oh, some Russian thugs took him from us.
哦，一些俄罗斯暴徒把从我们这里带走。
Oh you fucking guys!
哦，你他妈的你们！
Okay. No problem. We just have to get
him back.
好的。没问题。我们只需要把弄回来。
- From where?
- From the same place we took him from.
- 从哪里？
- 从把带走的同一个地方。
This monkey isn't just normal monkey.
这只猴子不是正常的猴子。
Every night, monkey drug mule.
每天晚上，猴子带着药物。
He take coke to buyer...
他带古柯硷给买方 ...
And deliver cash to dealer. He
middle man.
把现金交给毒品贩子。是中间人。
Dealer never handle drug directly.
毒品贩子从来没有直接处理药物。
He clean.
他很乾净。
- That's terrible.
- Not terrible. What he talking about. Fucking genius.
- 这真可怕。
- 并不可怕。他在说些什麽。他妈的天才。
You ever see monkey go to jail?
你见过猴子去坐牢吗？
We just take the monkey for deal, he come
close, we take his vest. That's that.
我们只是为了生意才抓猴子，他靠近了，我们拿他的背心。就是这样。
- We get some blow too, you know... bump.
- No, no more bumps, Chow.
- 我们也可以拿些吸的，你知道...炸弹。
- 不，不要炸弹，老周。
This is ridiculous.
这真是荒谬。
Stu, Mr. Chow can't whistle. Shake your
monkey.
史都，周先生不能吹口哨。叫一下猴子。
Alright, here we go.
好吧，我们走。
Come on!
来吧！
How did we wind up with the monkey
last night anyway?
我们昨晚是怎麽弄来猴子的呢？
I needed some blow and Alan thought
he was cute...
因为我需要一些炸弹 而艾伦觉得很可爱 ...
...so we stole him!
...所以我们就偷走！
So stupid!
这麽笨！
Stu, ready to grab vest?
史都，准备抢背心了？
- Okay. I just grab it?
- Yeah, just do it. Just do it.
- 好。我只要抓住它吗？
- 是啊，只是去做。只要做到这一点。
- Hey, little monkey.
- Alan, be quiet.
- 嘿，小猴子。
- 艾伦，安静。
- Fuck!
- We gotta go, right now!
- 靠！
- 我们得走了，现在！
- Pull that fuckin monkey in!
- I'm trying!
- 把那该死的猴子拉进来！
- 我试试！
Shit!
妈的！
- Get that monkey in here, Stu!
- He won't let go!
- 把那猴子抓过来这里，史都！
- 不放手！
Stu, get back in the car! Right now!
史都，快进来车上！现在！
I'm trying! Slow down!
我在努力！慢一点！
He's so strong!
好有力!
Let go you fuckin monkey!
放开 你他娘的猴子！
- Look out!
- Oh shit! Tight squeeze!
- 当心！
- 哦，干！抓紧！
I got him!
我得到了！
- Where's the code, Chow?
- Check his little vest.
- 号码在哪里，老周？
- 检查他的小背心。
- Got it, Alan?
- Yes, I got a .
- 找到吗，艾伦？
- 是的，我得到了。
- Slow down Chow!
- Hold on, J-Birds.
- 慢点，老周！
- 坐稳了，娘炮们！
Holy Shit!
真他妈的！
Don't worry. I got this shit!
别担心！哥能HOLD住！
Pig!
猪啊!
Oh, my word.
噢，我的天。
Sorry, Stu! My bad!
对不起，史都！我的错！
Oh, shit!
噢，该死！
Get down!
趴下！
What the fuck!
他妈的什么啊！
Oh no! He shot the monkey!
哦，不！他在射猴子！
They shot the monkey.
他们射中了猴子。
I'm at my wits end.
我束手无策了。
He's coming back around.
他又回来了
Look out!
当心！
- Holy fuck!
- Oh no...
- 他妈的！
- 哦，不...
- Everyone alright?
- Yeah.
- 每个人都还好吗？
- 是啊。
I have such an erection right now!
我现在有如此的勃起！
Are you for real?
你是说真的吗？
They're gonna take good care of you
here, ok.
他们会好好照顾你，好吧。
What's that?
那是什麽？
Oh, yeah. Cigarettes. Got em right here.
Here you go.
哦，是啊。香烟。放在这里。拿去吧。
Right here.
就在这里。
Deep breathe. Good.
深吸一口。好。
Soak it in.
吸进去
Breathe the smoke into your tiny
little lungs. There you go.
吸烟到你的小肺部里。吸吧。
It's funny. I've never been much of a
smoker, but...
这很有趣。我从来没有成为抽烟者，但...
Boy does it look cool on you.
它在你身上看起来很酷。
Alan, c'mon! Let's go!
艾伦，来吧！我们走吧！
I'll miss you, monkey.
我会想念你，猴子。
I wish monkeys could Skype.
我希望猴子能够使用Skype。
Maybe one day...
也许有一天...
Come on! Get in!
来吧！进来！
Are you guys seriously this calm?
你们还真冷静？
Relax, Stuart. It's classic switcheroo.
放松，史都尔特。这是典型的逆转胜。
I give him money, he gives us Teddy.
我给他钱，他给我们泰迪。
You ever do anything that doesn't end
up in a standoff, Chow?
你曾碰过事情搞僵後 无法收拾吗，老周？
I'm an international criminal. It always
ends like this.
我是一个国际罪犯。它总是会这样结束。
I met my wife at one of these things.
我在某件事时认识了我妻子。
- You got a wife?
- Yeah, we married 15 years.
- 你有妻子吗？
- 是啊，我们结婚 15年。
What, I not good looking enough for woman?
怎样，我是不够好看可以娶个女人？
No, that's cool.
不，这很酷。
Let's do this!
让我们来做吧！
- Welcome to the Tower Club.
- Blah blah blah, who cares.
- 欢迎来到塔俱乐部。
- 废话，废话，废话，谁在乎。
Stop! Chow crossing.
停！老周在靠近。
- Hey, Kingsley!
- Well, well.
- 嘿，金斯利！
- 好，好。
Propecia looking nice!
柔沛看起来不错！
You been hitting the gym?
你一直在健身房做健身？
Yes I am actually. Thank you for
noticing, Chow.
是的，真的有。谢谢你有注意到，老周。
Hey, guys. Have a seat.
嗨，夥计们。请坐。
- Where's Teddy?
- He's waiting downstairs in my car.
- 泰迪在哪里？
- 他在楼下我的车中等候。
Send him up when the transfer is complete.
当转帐完成 就送他上来。
Tell you what. Give me extra 50 grand, you
keep Teddy.
告诉你吧。给我额外的5万美元，你就把泰迪留着吧。
And I throw in this other fat fuck for free.
我再免费帮你增肥。
- Chow.. Chow...
- Could we move this along!
- 老周 ..老周 ...
- 我们可以快点进行吗！
Alan, account number. Come on, come on.
艾伦，帐号。来吧，来吧。
8-1-4, K as in knife, 2-3-9-8.
8-1-4，K 刀子knife的K，2-3-9-8。
- Password?
- "baloney1"
- 密码？
- 「baloney1」(一派胡言)
Your password is "baloney1" ?
您的密码是「baloney1」？
Well it used to be just "baloney" but
now they make you add number.
那麽 它曾经只是「胡扯」而已，但
现在他们要你加个号码。
Fuckin annoying.
他妈的烦人。
- And it's that easy.
- Ta dah!
- 这就是这麽简单。
- 哇赛！
Oh look. You sunk my battleship.
哦，看。你投资我的战舰。
- Great, now can we please have Teddy?
- Yeah. Bring him up.
- 太好了，现在我们可以有请泰迪？
- 是啊。带他上来。
See. We go to your wedding. We have fun. I
bust a nut.
看。我们去参加你的婚礼。我们会很好玩。我可以吃核果。
We did it, Stu. It's over!
我们成功了，史都。结束了！
This is Bangkok police! Everybody down!
这是曼谷员警！每个人趴下！
Oh, nuts!
哦，疯了！
Kingsley, you're fucking Five-O?
金斯利，你是他妈的条子？
Gotcha, Leslie!
没错，莱斯利！
Get him outta here.
把他带走。
Go! Just do it! Go!
走！快点走！走！
How the fuck...
日。。。
Samir, you fucked me over six grand?
You camel jockey!
萨米尔，你为了六百多美元坑我？
您这个骑骆驼的！
You spit on me?
你喷我！
Six grand this time, eight grand last time.
It's not the money, man, it's the principle!
这次六千，上次八千。这跟钱无关，兄弟，这是原则问题！
Principle? Nigga, please! We both dead inside.
原则？黑鬼，拜托你！我们内心早就没原则了。
Call me nigga... don't call me "nigga"!
叫?液诠?...不要叫我「黑鬼」！
- Put em in, motherfucker!
- He's an asshole, man.
-带他进来，狗日的！
-他是一个混球！
You guys ok?
你们好吗？
- What the fucks going on?
- Detective Inspector Peters, Interpol.
- 妈的怎麽回事？
- 探长彼得斯，国际刑警组织。
- You're a cop?
- Yes.
- 你是警察？
- 是的。
This sting operation has been in place
for weeks.
这卧底行动已进行几个星期了。
When Samir told us that your friend
was lost...
当萨米尔告诉我们，您的朋友丢了...
We took advantage of that information.
I'm sorry.
我们利用了这个资讯。我很抱歉。
- So can Teddy come out of the car now?
- No, Alan, Teddy's not in the fuckin car!
- 所以可以把泰迪从车里放出来吧？
- 不，艾伦，泰迪不在他妈的车里！
They don't have him. They never had him.
他们没有抓他。他们从来没有抓他。
They just needed us to bring them Chow.
They used Teddy as bait.
他们只是利用我们 把老周带来。
他们利用泰迪作为诱饵。
- Do you have any leads at all?
- No. We've checked everywhere.
- 你有什麽线索呢？
- 不，我们每个地方都查过了
No one has seen him. I'm sorry.
没有人见过他。我很抱歉。
If you haven't found him by now, I'm afraid
Bangkok has him.
如果你直到现在还没有找到他，我恐怕曼谷已经拥有他了。
Why do people keep saying that?
为什麽人们一直这麽说？
Stu... It's time.
史都 ...时间到了。
Alan...
史都 ...
-I'm sorry.
- Don't say that. Please.
- 我很抱歉。
- 不要这样说。
- No this time we really fucked up.
- Oh god! How bad?
- 不，这一次我们真的搞砸了。
- 哦，上帝！怎麽个糟法？
Like, no wedding bad?
像是，无法结婚？
Yeah... a little worse than that!
是啊...比这个再糟一点点！
Ok, how about this? He fell off
the fishing boat and drowned.
好了，这个怎麽样？他从渔船上摔下来 然後淹死。
No.
Ok, I got it. Teddy was hit by a truck.
好吧，我知道了。泰迪被卡车撞了。
- Alan!
- Not a good time, Phil. Kinda busy!
- 艾伦！
- 现在别找我，菲尔。我有点儿忙！
How many people get run over here?
这里有多少人被辗过？
- Over 1200 a year, Phil.
- Perfect!
- 每年1200人，菲尔。
- 太完美了
His body was too mangled to recover.
Case closed.
他的铺逡蛭损伤严重而无法复原。
结案。
Can I get more ice, please?
我可以要更多的冰吗，好吗？
I'm not gonna lie to Lauren.
我不想骗萝拉。
- Stu, do you want this or not?
- Look at what I've done, Phil. What I do.
- 史都，你到底要不要？
- 看我做了什麽，菲尔。我做了什麽。
I have a weakness for prostitutes. All
kinds, apparently.
我有召妓的缺点。各种妓女，很显然。
- I have a demon in me!
- So what?
- 我内心有一个魔鬼！
- 那又怎麽样呢？
Teddy's gone, but I can still save Lauren.
泰迪走了，但我还可以拯救萝拉。
Just let her live her life without me.
只要她的生活里没有我。
Stu!
I want you to call Doug and tell him I'm
never coming back.
我要你打电话 Doug 告诉他我一直没有回来。
Gettin off the hamster wheel.
要停止这种循环。
Gonna stay here in Bangkok.
I think I belong here.
我想留在曼谷。我觉得我属于这里。
Open up a little dentists office.
开一家小间牙医院。
Deep cleanings, with a happy ending.
帮人做深层清洗，结局快乐。
You sure about this?
你确定吗？
Hey, what the crud!
嘿，搞什麽飞机！
Powers out, Alan.
停电了，艾伦。
- Phil!
- Doug.
- 菲尔！
- 道格。
- I need answers, man.
- I know...
- 我需要回答，夥计。
- 我知道...
Doug, who are you talking to?
道格，你和谁说话？
- What?
- Give me the phone!
- 什麽？
- 给我电话！
Lauren, no! That's a private...
萝拉，不！这是一个私人...
Who is this?
是谁？
- Lauren?
- Phil? Tell me what's going on, right now!
- 萝拉？
- 菲尔？告诉我这是怎麽回事，马上！
We lost your little brother.
我们失去了你的小兄弟。
- What?
- Bangkok has him now.
- 什麽？
- 曼谷拥有他了。
You gotta take the stairs.
你必须走楼梯。
You're in Bangkok?
你在曼谷？
Ooh, that's a finger!
哦，这是一个手指！
Put Stu on the phone!
叫史都接手机！
Bangkok experiences 1500 power outages
per year.
曼谷每年停电1500次。
Stu really doesn't want to talk to anybody.
史都真的不想跟任何人谈话。
- Water everywhere. Powers out.
- 到处都是水。停电了。
Come on, Stu, use that big Jewish brain
来吧，史都，用用你的犹太人大脑
Phil! Give me the phone!
菲尔！把电话给我！
- It's Lauren! I got it! I'm handling it!
- I know.!
- 那是萝拉！我知道！我能处理！
- 我知道！
- Give me the fuckin...
- I can handle it, Stu!
- 把那妈的电话给我 ...
- 我可以处理，史都！
She's gonna break your heart!
她会伤了你的心！
Honey, sweetheart, it's me! I'm so sorry!
亲爱的，亲爱的，是我！我很抱歉！
Stu? What the hell is going on? What does he
mean you lost Teddy?
史都？这到底是怎麽回事？他说你失去泰迪是什麽意思？
What? Is that what Phil said?
No no no. We misplaced, Teddy.
什麽？这就是菲尔说的吗？不不不。我们跟泰迪约错了。
But we're all good now. We heading back to the
hotel. We're gonna see you soon!
但是我们都没事了。我们将回酒店了。很快看到您！
I love you so much! And I gotta go, but
I'll see you soon. Bye.
我如此爱你！ 但我得走了，很快回去。再见。
Stu!
史都！
- Stu!
- God!
Taxi!
计程车！
Come on, Alan!
来吧，艾伦！
Hey, you mind filling us in!
嘿，你可以跟我们说说吧！
Ok, now when we woke up, the power was out.
好了，现在当我们醒来时，停电了。
And you found Teddy's finger in what?
而你发现 泰迪的手指在哪吗？
- In a pool of water.
- But it didn't start out as water.
- 在水盆中。
- 但里面并没有融成水。
No, it was ice.
不，里面是冰。
Exactly! Teddy got ice from the machine...
没错！泰迪从制冰机里拿了冰...
...came back to the room. Put his finger
on ice and fell asleep.
...回到房间。把他的手指冰起来 就又去睡了。
Now what do you do if you wake up...
现在，你会怎麽做，如果你醒来 .....
...and you find your finger floating in
a bowl of melted ice?
.....，你发现你的手指漂浮一碗融化的冰？
I'd get more ice, Stu... on the 15th
fuckin floor!
我会去拿更多的冰，史都 ... 他妈的15楼！
Yes! Teddy goes up, the power goes out...
是啊！泰迪上楼时，停电了 ...
- Holy shit! Of course!
- He's at the ice machine.
- 我的妈阿！当然！
- 他在制冰机。
Alan, no!
艾伦，不！
It's on ten!
电梯是在十楼！
- Sir, is the elevator stuck?
- ??.
- 先生，电梯卡住了？
- 是。
- C'mon!
- Go, go, go!
- 来吧！
- 走吧，走吧，走吧！
Hey, Teddy!
嘿，泰迪！
Look out, look out!
当心，当心！
- Teddy!
- You're ok!
- 泰迪！
- 你还好吧！
Teddy, you okay? You ok, man?
泰迪，你没事吧？你没事吧，夥计？
- Where am I?
- You're in an elevator, in the middle of Bangkok.
- 我在哪里？
- 你在电梯里，曼谷的一个地方。
But we're gonna get you outta here. It's
gonna be fine.
但是我们会带你离开这儿。一切会没事的。
Hey Stu, nice tattoo.
嘿 史都，漂亮的纹身。
Thanks, man.
谢谢你，夥计。
Alright, let's do this! C'mon, c'mon!
好吧，我们走吧！来吧，来吧！
Tell him we found him.
Yeah, I know. But we're on our way. Ok, bye!
告诉他，我们找到了他了。是啊，我知道。但是我们在回去路上。好吧，再见！
Alright, guests are arriving, people starting
to ask questions, but we can still pull this off!
好吧，客人正在抵达，人们开始问问题，但我们仍然可以搞定的！
- How?
- I don't know, with a taxi?
- 如何？
- 我不知道，坐计程车吗？
- Chow's speed boat.
- What?
- 老周的快艇。
- 什麽？
Last think I remember, was getting off
Chow's speed boat.
最後我想我记得，我们从老周的快艇下船。
- Chow has a speed boat?
- "The Perfect Life".
- 老周有快艇？
- 叫「完美生活」。
C'mon!
来吧！
Stu, get that back line.
史都，把缆绳解开。
Good jump, Phil!
跳的好，菲尔！
- You alright?
- Yeah.
- 你还好吗？
- 是啊。
- You sure you know how to drive this thing?
- 你确定你知道如何驾驶这东西？
Please, I was raised in a yacht club. I
know what I'm doing.
拜托，我从小在一个游艇俱乐部长大。我
知道我在做什麽。
You know where we're going?
你知道我们要去哪里吗？
Leave it to the Captain!
全部交给船长！
Oh fuck you, Alan!
哦，你他妈的，艾伦！
Do you know where we're going, Captain?
你知道我们要去哪里吗，船长？
Affirmative cadet!
We're going south.
当然知道 见习生！ 我们往南方。
- We're in the Gulf of Thailand.
- Good.
- 我们在泰国湾。
- 非常好。
Hey! You okay?
嘿！你没事吧？
- Feeling a little better.
- Alright!
- 感觉好一点了。
- 好吧！
Listen Teddy. I'm really sorry! We didn't
mean for any of this to happen.
听着 泰迪。我真的很抱歉！我们没有想到会有这种情况发生。
It's funny. I can't remember anything
But... when I woke up, I was kinda happy.
这很有趣。我什麽都不记得 但是...当我醒来时，我还挺高兴。
Yeah!
是啊！
By the way... Do you have any idea
where my finger is?
顺便说一下...你知道我的手指在哪儿吗？
Yeah, we gave it to a drug dealing
monkey.
是啊，我们给了一只做毒品交易的猴子。
Bangkok...
在曼谷...
Yeah, right... fuckin Bangkok!
是的，正确。。。狗日的曼谷！
I apologize. There will be no wedding!
我道歉。将不会有婚礼了！
He is on his way. He will be here...
他在路上。他会到这里的。。。
Please, if you will all move to the bar.
We are going to clear this area.
拜托大家，如果你们全部移到酒吧去。
那我们要清理这个区域了。
Please!
请！
I'm telling you, I spoke to him. He's coming.
我告诉你，我和他说过话。他要回来了。
Look! There they are!
瞧！他们在那里
Stu!
史都！
- Alan, there's no dock.
- Just hang on!
- 艾伦，这里没有码头。
- 那就坚持一下吧！
- Alan, it's not funny! Turn the boat!
- Hang on!
- 艾伦，这不有趣！把船转回去！
- 坚持！
- Is that Alan driving the boat?
- What?
- 是艾伦在驾驶船吗？
- 什麽？
Uh, we should probably move back a little bit.
嗯，那我们也许应该退後一点点。
Oh my god!
天哪！
Turn the boat!
把船转头！
Everyone back up a little bit here.
每个人都退後一点点。
Sir, it's gonna get worse before it gets better.
先生，事情在变得更好之前 会先变得更糟 。
Hi! Hi everybody!
嗨！大家好！
Came in a little hotter than we planned.
I'm sorry we trenched the lawn here.
这比我们预计的还要过来一点点。
对不起，我们占据了这块草坪。
Totally fixable. A little bit of sod, it'll
be fine.
完全可以解决的。一点点的草皮而已，没关系。
- Baby!
- Oh my god!
- 宝贝！
- 噢，我的上帝！
I'm so happy to see you!
我好高兴见到你！
- Teddy! Teddy here.
- Hi, Dad!
- 泰迪！泰迪 过来。
- 嗨，爸爸！
- You alright?
- Yeah, ok.
- 你还好吗？
- 是啊，好吧。
- Your hand!
- I know.
- 你的手！
- 我知道。
We had an accident. I'm ok.
我们出了意外。我还好。
This is your fault!
这都是你的错！
- Dad.
- He's right. I have not been completely honest.
- 爸爸。
- 他是对的。我并不是完全地诚实。
- Stu? Don't do this.
-Yeah?
- 史都？别这样做。
-是吗？
Thanks, Phil, but gonna do it.
谢谢你，菲尔，但还是得这麽做。
You said I'm a joke.Well I'm not.
你说我是米汁. 但我不是。
I'm not some weird, milky, ricy, watery
that you feed to infants and old people, ok!
我不是有点怪异，奶状的，米做的，水样的 拿来喂婴儿和老人的，好吗！
Maybe I would be if you added some
cayenne pepper!
也许我会是，如果你添加了一些辣椒的话！
I wish I was a boring dentist...
我希望我是一个无聊的牙医 ...
...who had a boring life and boring friends...
...拥有无聊乏味的生活和朋友...
... but I don't and I'm not.
...但我不是，我也没有。
I'm actually part of this weird wolf pack.
实际上，我的一部分是奇怪的狼群。
It's not weird. It's pretty cool
actually. No membership fees.
这不奇怪。这实际上很酷。我们不收会员费。
I've had enough of this. Come here.
我已经受够了。到这里来。
Whoa! Here's the deal man.
哇！好一个大人物。
- I got a dark side!
- 我有黑暗的一面！
There's a demon in me!
我体内有一个魔鬼(demon)！
It's true, he has semen in him.
这是真的，他体内有精液(semen)。
I said demon.
我说的是恶魔(demon)。
- But you also have semen in you, remember?
- Not relevant, but thank you, Alan.
- 但你也有精液 记得吗？
- 这不相干，但是谢谢你，艾伦。
The point is, this demon takes me to
some pretty weird places.
问题是，这个恶魔带我去一些非常奇怪的地方。
We lost Teddy for two days in Bangkok.
我们在曼谷 失去了泰迪两天。
But that same demon took us to
hell and back to find him.
但同样的恶魔带我们到地狱并找回他。
We took on Bangkok and we won.
我们对抗曼谷 而我们赢了。
Now that's pretty fuckin cool if you ask me!
现在，如果你问我 我可是很他妈的非常冷静！
I love your daughter, and I'm
gonna marry her.
我爱你的女儿，我也会娶她。
- Unless you have any problem with that?
- I'm good.
- 除非你有什麽问题吗？？
- 我很好。
But all that said, it would actually mean
a great deal to both of us...
但是，大家都这麽说，实际上这对我们来说是重要的...
...if we could just get your mother fucking
blessing!
...如果我们可以得到你妈的祝福！
Hey, Alan...
嘿，艾伦 ...
- That looks pretty cool shaved.
- Thanks, Phil.
- 剃光头这看起来很酷。
- 谢谢，菲尔。
You should shave your head too.
你也应该剃光头了。
- Why would I do that?
- Well than we would look exactly alike.
- 为什麽我要这麽做？
- 嗯，这样我们看上去会一模一样。
- Take good care of my daughter, Stu.
- I will.
- 照顾好我的女儿，史都。
- 我会的。
I'm sorry we almost killed everyone with
the boat.
对不起，那艘船差点杀死每个人。
Just happy you're here.
好高兴只要你在这里。
And don't worry about the tattoo. I'm gonna
have it lasered as soon as we're home in LA.
也不要担心纹身。一回洛杉矶我会尽快的用雷射清除它。
- That's ok. I can get used to it.
- Really?
- 没关系。我能适应它的。
- 真的吗？
But for now, let's switch sides?
但现在，让我们换个位置？
- Yeah, ok.
- Thank you.
- 是啊，好吧。
- 谢谢你。
Much better.
好多了。
Dear family and friends. On behalf of Stu and Lauren...
亲爱的家人和朋友。代表史都和萝拉 ...
...I welcome all of you, to this
marriage celebration.
...我欢迎你们，这场结婚庆典。
We are here today to...
今天我们在这里 ...
Hey buddy. Can you hold on for a second.
嗨，老兄。你能暂停一下子吗。
Thank you.
Hello? Hi everyone!
哈罗？大家好！
My name's Alan Garner.
我叫艾伦加纳。
I want to thank the Asiatic people for
allowing us in your land.
我要感谢亚洲人民 让我们站在你们的土地上。
I wanted to say that, um, I'm really
happy to be here...
我想说，嗯，我真的很高兴在这里 ...
...and I have a wedding gift to present
to Lauren and Stu.
...我有一个结婚礼物要送给萝拉和史都。
And um, a lot of thought has gone into this...
嗯，它代表了许多的意义 ...
...and I hope that you appreciate it as
much as I did, or going to.
...我希望你能像我一样地欣赏它，或者将欣赏它。
Okay, guys!
好吧，大夥们！
Oh, fuck!
哦，他妈的！
Alan!
艾伦！
What the fuck?
这是什麽他妈的？
- So what do ya think?
- That's insane! How did you do that?
- 所以你觉得如何？
- 这是疯了！你是怎麽做到的？
My dad had to make a lot of calls.
我爸爸不得不打了很多的电话。
I told Mike that you gotta do it. It's
for my third best friend.
我告诉迈克，你总是得做的。这是给我的三个最好的朋友。
Alan, it's amazing!
I love it! Thank you so much!
艾伦，这太神奇了！我喜欢它！谢谢你！
We only have him for tonight. We don't
have him permanently.
我们只有今晚能请到他。我们不能一直唱下去。
Understood!
理解！
- You do a lot of public speaking, Alan?
- I barely ??
- 你做过很多次的公众演讲，艾伦？
- 我几乎没有过？？
Mike, you were great. It's true, that
was incredible.
迈克，你真是伟大。这是真的，那真是难以置信
Thanks, guys. That means a lot, really!
谢谢你们。对我意义重大，真的！
By the way, you really need to remove that
fuckin tattoo from your face!
顺便说一下，你真的需要从你的脸上移除他妈的纹身！
Yeah! On it!
是啊！会做的！
Sorry about the last minute change up
to the performance, Mike.
很抱歉在最後一刻改变了节目，迈克。
- Don't worry, Alan.
- What are you talking about?
- 别担心，艾伦。
- 你在说什麽？
Well he was originally supposed to sing
"Burning Up" by the Jonas Brothers...
他原本应该唱乔纳斯兄弟的「烧起来」...
...but then I remembered you don't like indie rock.
...可是我记得你不喜欢独立摇滚。
Hey guys. You're not gonna believe this.
嘿，大家。你们不会相信这个的。
- Is that your phone?
- Yeah.
- 那是你的电话吗？
- 是啊。
How come you never tried calling us?
你怎麽从来没有想过要打电话给我们呢？
It's been dead for two days.
它已经停机两天了。
But I recharged it and found all
these photos.
但我重新充电後发现这些照片。
What?
什麽？
- Shit!
- Yeah, some of it's pretty messed up.
- 妈的！
- 是呀，有些是相当混乱的。
- Awesome, let's check em out.
- Whoa, whoa, whoa!
- 真棒，让我们检查看看。
- 哇，哇，哇！
No one needs to see this stuff!
没有人需要看到这种东西！
C'mon man! I'm Mike Tyson. I've seen everything!
来吧，兄弟！我是Mike泰森。我已经看到了一切了！
- It'll be fine.
- (mumbles something)
- 没事的。
- (喃喃自语)
- Alright, we look at it once.
- And then we delete them. It's gonna be ok.
- 好吧，我们再看一次。
- 然後我们删除掉。没关系的。
- Oh, ooh!
- Mother fucker!
- 哦，哦！
- 操他妈的！